<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Explore_Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="first_slide_title">Search Your location</string>
    <string name="second_slide_title">Make a Call</string>
    <string name="third_slide_title">Add Missing Place</string>
    <string name="fourth_slide_title">Sit Back And Enjoy</string>
    <string name="fifth_slide_title">------------------------------------------------</string>

    <string name="first_slide_desc">You can Search any place nearby or within Maharashtra. We will display specific or all search related result.</string>
    <string name="second_slide_desc">We provide  almost all thr numbers of all department and shop registerd with us. You can make call with those department</string>
    <string name="third_slide_desc">If you have a shop or something and want to be a part of our growing industry then add your place by your Own.</string>
    <string name="fourth_slide_desc">We will handle everything for you. As you have the app in your pocket then you do not have to worry.</string>

    <!-- Temple Name-->
    <string name="chatur">Chattushringi Temple</string>
    <string name="jejuri">Jejuri Temple</string>
    <string name="moreshwar">Moreshwar Temple</string>


    <!-- PuneForts Info-->

    // title
    <string name="hist">History</string>
    <string name="dist">Distance</string>
    <string name="reach">How to reach?</string>
    <string name="time">Opening Time</string>
    <string name="Spec">Speciality</string>

    //History
    <string name="sinh_hist">The Sinhagad Fort was initially known as Kondhana after the sage Kaundinya. The Kaundinyeshwar temple coupled with the caves and carvings indicates that the fort had probably been built around two thousand years ago. It was seized by Muhammad bin Tughlaq from the Koli king Nag Naik in 1328 AD. Shahaji Bhosale, as the commander of Ibrahim Adil Shah II, was entrusted with the control of the Pune region. His son Shivaji, refused to accept the Adilshahi and initiated the task of setting up Swarajya. Shivaji gained control of Kondana in 1647 by convincing Siddi Amber, the Adilshahi Sardar who controlled the fort, that he, the son of Shahaji Bhosale, could manage the forts defences optimally.</string>
    <string name="shiv_hist">The present day Junnar was known as Jirna-nagar, Junner and existed prior to beginning of year AD. Junnar was capital of King Nahapan from Shak dynasty. The Satvahan king Satkarni, a son of Gautami, wiped out Shakas and held dominance over Junnar and its surrounding area. excavated many caves. After Satvahan, Shivneri fort came under the control of Chalukya of Rashtrakut Empire. Yadavas established their rule between 1170 to 1308. During this tenure Shivneri was built as a fort. In 1443 Malik Ul Tujar defeated Yadavas and conquered the fort. Thus the fort came under the control of Bahamani Empire.</string>
    <string name="tik_hist">Not much is known about who build this fort. A vihara can be found on the fort which estimates the fort to be in existence since the 7 or 8th century A.D.In 1585, Malik Ahmad Nizam Shah I conquered the fort and annexed it to the Nizam territory. Chatrapati Shivaji Maharaj won over the forts of Lohagad, Karnala, Mahuli, Songad, Visapur and Tala in 1657. He successfully conquered the Nizam territory of Konkan and bought it under his rule.</string>
    <string name="tung_hist">Tung Fort was built before 1600 CE. It was built by the Adil Shahi dynasty but was captured by Shivaji. It is a small fort, and able to hold not more than 200 troops at a time. As such, it would not have been able to defend itself on its own for a long time. Its shape and structure suggest that its main function was as a watchtower overlooking Maval region of the Pawana and Mulshi valleys guarding the road to Pune city. The Dhamale family, one of the Deshmukh from the Maval region, was charged with ensuring the security of Tung Fort. During invasion, it served to provide a temporary distraction for invaders. Thus, the major forts of Visapur and Lohagad would have time to prepare themselves to meet the invading army.</string>
    <string name="roh_hist">Rohida or Vichitragad is a fort situated in Rohid maval which is in Bhor region of Pune districtRohida was built by the Yadavas. In  1656, this fort was captured by  Shivaji Maharaj. In 1666, the Moghuls conquered the fort but could not hold it for long.Again on June 24, 1670, Shivaji Maharaj recaptured the fort.This fort is situated in the southern part of Pune. The place where Rohida is situated is a stratergically important as this region of Pune is near by  Satara and also well connected with Kokan  by many ghat routes</string>
    <string name="raj_hist">Shivaji seized the fort in 1656, then known as the fort of Rairi from Chandraraoji More, the king of Jawali. Shivaji renovated and expanded the fort of Rairi and renamed it as Raigad (Kings Fort). It became the capital of Shivajis Maratha kingdom.The villages of Pachad  Raigadwadi are located at the base of the Raigad fort. These two villages were considered very important during the Maratha rule in Raigad. The actual climb to the top of the Raigad fort starts from Pachad. During Shivajis rule, A cavalry of 10,000 was always kept on standby in Pachad village. Shivaji also built another fort Lingana around 2 miles away from Raigad. The Lingana fort was used to keep prisoners</string>
    <string name="ghan_hist">A 300 years old structure situated near Tamhini Ghat and Mulshi, it is said that Ghangad Fort used to be a prison under the kingdom of Peshwas. And apparently, it was also the watchtower for the city of Pune. Unfortunately, there is not much historical evidence supporting this fact. However, what the fort is sure to offer is the views for the lush green region from the very top. Ghangad fort is a popular trekking destination amongst residents of Pune, Mumbai, and Nagpur. The trek is a medium to easy level trek which on average takes about an hour to reach the midpoint of the fort</string>
    <string name="kot_hist">The cave and the temple carvings date back to the 13th century. Not much is known about the history until the 18th century. In 1684 Aurangjeb sent Abdul Kadir and AlaiBiradkar to capture this fort. After a small skirmish, the fort was captured by Abdul Kadir. Aurangjeb honored Abdul Kadir and renamed this fort as Miftah-ul-Fateh (Key to success). Many attempts were made later to win this fort by the Maratha Army, but they were not successful. In 1716, this cave was captured by the British. On 2 November 1817, it was recaptured by the Marathas under the leadership of Bapurao who was general of Bajirao Peshwa. The fort was recaptured by the British on 30 December 1817, by Captain Brooks. The British had the fort till 1862 as an outpost for vigilance on the surrounding valley and the hills all around it</string>
    <string name="prat_hist">The Maratha ruler Chhatrapati Shivaji maharaj commissioned Moropant Trimbak Pingle, his prime minister, to undertake the construction of this fort in order to defend the banks of the Nira and the Koyna rivers, and to defend the Par pass.It was completed in 1656.[3] The Battle of Pratapgad between Shivaji and Afzal Khan was fought below the ramparts of this fort on 10 November 1659. This was the first major test of the fledgling kingdoms army, and set the stage of the establishment of the Maratha empire. Pratapgad continued to be involved in regional politics.</string>
    <string name="ram_hist">Constructed by the Satavahanas, the historical Rajmachi fort complex has an interesting history. Shivaji Maharaj captured this fort in 1657 and also the surrounding forts from the Adilshahi ruler of Bijapur. The Mughal Emperor Aurangzeb again seized the fort from the Marathas in 1704. The very next year, the Marathas regained its control and later in 1713, Shahu Maharaj gave over the Rajmachi fort to Kanhoji Angre. With the downfall of the Marathas in 1818, the British took over the control of the Maratha territories and also the Rajmachi fort.</string>

    <!--how to reach-->
    //Sinhgad fort
    <string name="sinh_reach"> Pune Railway Station is the nearest of all the stations to get to the Sinhagad Fort. From here, you can either opt for a private cab service or choose for local bus transport to take you to the fort</string>
    <string name="sinh_reach1"> Your journey from Pune to Sinhagad will be for an hour and 15 minutes. You can opt for a private cab service or Uber cab service or Ola to drive you between the two points.</string>
    <string name="sinh_reach2"> Plenty of bus services are there to drive you between these two points. You need to visit the Pune Bus Stand to find the buses to prefer.</string>

    //Shivneri fort
    <string name="shiv_reach">The Pune airport and the Chhatrapati Shivaji International Airport are the nearest airports from Shivneri. Both of them connect to the city Junnar. After reaching Junnar tourists can take a cab or bus to travel to the Shivneri fort.</string>
    <string name="shiv_reach1">At about a distance of 94 km from the Shivneri Fort is the Pune railway station. From this station several private cars are available which help the tourists to reach the Shivneri Fort. Another railway station which connects Junnar at a distance of about 82 km is the Talegaon Dabhade railway station. State buses are available from this station to reach the city and then to the fort.</string>
    <string name="shiv_reach2">The Junnar city is well connected by state buses with many major towns of Maharashtra like Thane, Mumbai, Pune, etc. It takes about half an hour walk to reach the bottom of the fort from the city. One can also hire a car from Junnar and climb up to the fort. The Shivneri Fort can also be reached from Mumbai using the Mumbai Pune Expressway. One can also avail the old Mumbai road from Pune to reach the fort.</string>

    //Tikona Fort
    <string name="tik_reach2">Several buses are running between Mumbai or Pune and Tikona Fort. In case you are travelling here in your private car or bike, you may opt for NH48 and then redirect yourself on Pavana Nagar Kamshet Road. This road will drive you to the Tikona Peth. </string>
    <string name="tik_reach3">Lohegaon is the nearest airport to reach Tikona Fort. After that, you can opt either for the local bus or rental cab service to drop you to the Tikona Peth. </string>

    //Tung Fort
    <string name="BY_train">Lonavala railway station is the closest from Tung Fort. Visitors will simply need to take local taxi or bus from Lonavala railway station to Tung Fort.</string>
    <string name="By_bus">Travelers will need to reach Lonavala first. From here they can catch a bus that stops at the nearest bus stop to Tung Fort, GhusalKhamb. And finally, a walk of almost 1.5 km from GhusalKhumb will take you to Tung Fort. </string>
    <string name="by_bike">A Lot of visitors from across the states come to visit Tung Fort by motorbike. Simply reach Lonavala and ride towards Aamby Valley. Approximately an hour from Lonavala is the Tung Village where the fort can be found. </string>
    <string name="By_air">The Closest airport from Tung Fort is the Pune International Airport. From here local cab and taxi service are available to the fort.</string>
    <string name="By_car">The distance from Lonavala to Tung Fort is just 23 km and will only take about an hour by car. If you are with your family or in a group, this is a good option.</string>

    //Rohida Fort
    <string name="by_road">If you are making your way from Pune, we recommend you to catch the NH4 highway and turn towards Bhor. After the Kapurhol phata on the NH4, you will come across a diversion to the right which will take you to Bhor. After you get on your path to Bhor, you need to head over to Bajarwadi Village. Bajarwadi Village is Rohida fort’s base village. You can park your personal vehicles at Primary School at Bajarwadi.
    </string>

    //Rajgad Fort
    <string name="raj_rail">You can catch a direct train to Pune railway station and then from there, you can either hire a direct cab or public transport to reach Pali. The distance between Pune railway station and Pali village is 68 km.</string>
    <string name="raj_road">The village of Pali is easily accessible by road. From the village, you need to trek up the hill to reach the fort.</string>
    <string name="raj_air">The nearest airport to the fort is located in Pune at a distance of around 75 km. Once you have reached Pune, you can either hire a direct cab or use public transport to reach Pali, which is a small village at the base of the hills and it is the place from where one needs to trek up the hill. </string>

    //Ghangad Fort

    <string name="ghan_rail">The cheapest way of reaching here is on a train journey. Visitors can board a train to Lonavala from Mumbai or Pune which is the closest railway station at a distance of 35 kilometers from the fort. Thereafter, using public transportation, you can further reach Bhamburde.</string>
    <string name="ghan_road">If one wishes to take the roadways, the Lonavala-Aamby valley route offers scenic views and is pretty well maintained. Similarly, Tamhini Ghat Route is an alternate route option. The way to Ghangad Fort takes one through the scenic hills of Sahyadris, thus a road trip is recommended for driving or riding enthusiasts.</string>
    <string name="ghan_air">Mumbai airport is the closest airport to the fort.</string>


    //Kothaligad Fort
    <string name="kot_air">The nearest airport to the fort is located in Mumbai at a distance of about 95 km. Once you have reached Mumbai, you can either hire a direct cab or use the public transport to reach the fort. </string>
    <string name="kot_rail">If you are looking forward to travelling by rail, then the best way is to take a direct train to Karjat railway station and then from there, a cab to the base of the fort. From the base, you need to trek up the hill to reach the fort. The distance between the fort and Karjat is 28 km.</string>
    <string name="kot_road">The region around Kothaligad is well connected to all other cities and towns by road.</string>

    //pratapgad Fort
    <string name="prat_road">Buses or private cars can be availed to reach Pratapgad fort, from the airports or the railway stations. A lot of tourist also hire bikes and enjoy the ride as they travel up the curved roads of the hill station.</string>
    <string name="prat_air">By plane one can reach to Paro, the only international airport of the country. It is just near about 1 hour from Thimphu.</string>
    <string name="prat_train">The major railways junction near Pratapgad is Pune, at a distance of 142 kilometres. Two other major junctions include Miraj, 170 kilometres, and Sangli, 165 kilometres from Pratapgad. The nearest railroad, however, is Satara, situated at a distance of about 15 kilometres from the Pratapgad fort.</string>

    //Rajmachi Fort
    <string name="raj_train">From Mumbai you can get a local train to Pune and get down at Karjat. From Shree Ram Bridge at Karjat, hire a shared auto to reach Kondana village. It is the base of Rajmachi trek from where you have to walk for around 3 to 4 hours to reach the summit.</string>
    <string name="raj_bus">There are two road routes from Mumbai up to Rajmachi. From Mumbai you can drive up to Kondhane side and trek a longer distance for 3- 4 hours to reach Rajmachi.

The other route is from Pune/Lonavala where you have to drive till the Udhewadi base village and trek a shorter distance for 30-40 minutes. Both the roads are a bit rough and the Pune route is more hazardous during monsoon.
</string>
    <string name="raj_Air">The nearest airport to Rajmachi is Mumbai International Airport which is connected to the major cities of India and abroad by regular flights. From the airport you can take a train or bus to Lonavala or Karjat. The Pune International Airport also operates regular flights to the major cities of India and abroad and is at a distance of 173 Km from Rajmachi</string>


    <!--Best time to visit-->
    //Sinhgad fort
    <string name="sinh_sum">With sweltering heat reining the summers in Sinhagad, it is advisable not to visit the place during this season. The hot and uncomfortable summer season kick-starts from the month of March and extends up to the mid of June with temperatures rising up to 42 degree Celsius during the daytime</string>
    <string name="sinh_mansoon">Beginning from the month of June and ending by September, monsoons bring along some respite from the sweltering heat of the summers. The recorded rainfall ranges something between 22 degree Celsius and 28 Degree Celsius. Monsoon is one of the apt, amongst the three seasons to visit Sinhagad.</string>
    <string name="sinh_Winter">Kick-starting from the month of November, winter is the best time to visit the fort. Sinhagad is best experienced with some biting cold temperatures of 19 degree doing the rounds, and the placid cool breeze flowing across the face.</string>
    //Shivneri Fort
    <string name="shiv_sum">The summer season starts from March and continues till May and the temperature ranges between 22 to 38 degree Celsius. The place experiences maximum heat in the months of April and May.</string>
    <string name="shiv_mansoon">Monsoon sets in from the beginning of June and continues till the month of October. The area receives moderate rainfall and heavy showers are seen in the months of July and August. There are even landslides and floods during monsoons. Thus it is recommended that tourists avoid this place during the rainy season.</string>
    <string name="shiv_winter">Winter starts from November till the month of January. The temperature goes down to 11 degree Celsius during December and January. The months of October and March are best time to plan holiday in this place. The climate is pleasant and tourists can explore the fort comfortably.</string>
    //Tikona fort
    <string name="tik_sum">Summers are hot and humid here. You can expect the temperature to range from 25 to 35 degrees. Locals plan night trekking here to beat the heat of summer. This being an off-season for tourist activities, you will easily find the best affordable stay options here.</string>
    <string name="tik_mansoon">The period between June to September is reserved for the showers. The weather remains pleasant, and the region gets covered with lush green forest stretch. Although it is not advisable to trek at Tikona during monsoons, the natural beauty here in this season is truly outstanding.</string>
    <string name="tik_winter">The months between October to March mark the winter season in Tikona. Winter temperature ranges from 11 to 25 degrees. As the monsoon clouds start fading away, what remains behind is the lush green hills covered with a blanket of dew.</string>

    //Tung Fort
    <string name="tung_sum">Summer in this part of Maharashtra lasts from March all the way to June. The temperatures during this time can rise up to 45°C and the trek through the Tung Fort can get really difficult. Additionally, there are no restaurants or snack corners around the place, so you will need to carry enough food and water.</string>
    <string name="tung_mansoon">During the rainy season which is between July and September, the fort is capsized with glowing green tropics and shimmering water bodies. Although trekking can be a bit risky due to the wetland, the risk is completely appreciated by the magnificent view of the Pawan lake and incredible landscapes. </string>
    <string name="tung_winter">One of the best times to visit the fort, winter at Tung Fort ranges between October and February. Around this time the weather is dry with a hint of haze enveloping the top of the fort which provides an extraordinary view. Furthermore, the visitors are advised to wear and carry proper trekking equipment as during early mornings the fort can be moist and slippery in winter.</string>

    //Rohida Fort
    <string name="roh_mansoon">If you want to know when’s the best time to visit this fort, then we might recommend you to visit this place during the monsoon season.Winter</string>
    <string name="roh_winter">If you are someone who loves camping, then you can visit this place during the winter season as camping during the winter season is considered to be breath taking. Stargazing as well as cooking some delicious food over a bonfire is a blissful experience</string>


    //Rajgad Fort
    <string name="raj_man">Trekking feels fantastic during the monsoons but trekkers should take precautions as the trek route gets very slippery.</string>
    <string name="raj_win">Winter season is ideal for camping at the fort. The temperatures get very low during the winters and a bonfire based campsite is a heavenly experience.</string>

    //Ghangad Fort
    <string name="ghan_sum">The summer months of March to June start are very hot and humid in the Sahyadris and must be avoided. </string>
    <string name="ghan_mansoon">The monsoon months of June, July, August until mid September bring out the most scenic views of the Sahyadris. The western ghats bloom with lush greenery. However, due to the rains that also bring out foggy clouds, visibility is not the same every day.</string>
    <string name="ghan_winter">October to February months of winters has pleasant weather for adventure activities like trekking or hiking. And here amidst the Western ghats, the fort also offers clearer views of the sky and the surrounding region. Thus, nature lovers interested in landscapes may want to visit during the winter season.</string>


    //Kothaligad fort
    <string name="kot_sum">Summer is absolutely NO, since its too tiring to walk from Ambivali till Peth as well as the views are not that great in summer, due to no greenery, no waterfalls and no mist.</string>
    <string name="kot_mon">Monsoon will be the best time to visit due to low temperatures, greenery, misty clouds and waterfall views.</string>
    <string name="kot_win">Winter is too cold, you can enjoy morning mist and fog all around the fort.</string>

    //Pratapgad Fort
    <string name="prap_sum">March to June is the summer season of the place. Being a hill station, the temperature is moderate even in summers. Temperature can vary from 15° to 35° Celsius. Summer is the best time to visit Pratapgad.</string>
    <string name="prap_mon">Rains exhibit the greenest best sight of Pratapgad. June to September is the time for monsoon. However, be careful with your steps if you are climbing the stairs of the fort, as they can get slippery due to rain./</string>
    <string name="prap_win">Winter months are December to February. Temperature may go down to 10° Celsius, and the maximum can be 24° Celsius.</string>

    //Rajmachi Fort
    <string name="raj_sum">March to May is the summer season when the temperature ranges between 21 to 35 degrees Celsius.</string>
    <string name="raj_mon">Monsoon sets in Rajmachi in June and continues through September. Temperature ranges between 24 to 29 degrees Celsius and the entire landscape is covered under a blanket of greenery.</string>
    <string name="raj_Win">Winter in Rajmachi is quite pleasant and being a dry season, it is convenient to walk along the forest trails. Winter is also the perfect time for outdoor camping and stargazing when the outside temperature comes down to 17 degrees Celsius.</string>


    <!--Pune Temples Info-->

    //Description
    <string name="dagadu_desd">The deity of Lord Ganesha was incepted by Shri Dagdusheth Halwai and his wife Lakshmibai way back, when they lost their only son to the plague epidemic. Every year, the Ganpati festival was celebrated with deep faith and enthusiasm, not only by Dagdusheth’s family but the entire neighbourhood. Tatyasaheb Godse, then in his early youth, was a zestful participant in the celebrations</string>
    <string name="alandi_desc">Alandi has a long history but gained prominence in the 13th century when Dnyaneshwar (1275–1296) decided to entomb, otherwise known as sanjeevan samadhi, himself in a samadhi, a form of shrine, under the then existing Siddheshwar temple complex in 1296. A temple was built over the Samadhi by Ambekar Deshpande in around 1580–1600. Further additions to the temple were made during the Maratha Empire era by Maratha nobles and the Peshwa.</string>
    <string name="bhim_desc">Bhimashankar Temple is a Jyotirlinga shrine located 50 km Khed taluka (alias Rajgurunagar), near Pune, in Maharashtra, India. It is located 127 km from Shivajinagar (in Pune) in the Ghat region of the Sahyadri Mountains. Bhīmāshankar is also the source of the river Bhima, which flows southeast and merges with the Krishna river near Raichur. The other Jyotirlinga shrines in Maharashtra are Trimbakeshwar near Nashik and Grishneshwar.</string>
    <string name="chat_desc">Chattushringi goddess in the reigning deity of the city of PuneShe is also known as Mahakalee, Mahalakshmee, Mahasaraswatee and Ambareshwari allies Shri Devi Chattushringi..Her temple is situated on the slopes of a mountain in the North-West of Pune.This is in the midst of natures scenic beauty. This 90 ft. high and 125 ft. wide temple is looked after by Shri Devi Chattushringi Mandir Trust .</string>
    <string name="jejuri_desc">Jejuri is a city and a municipal council in Pune district in the Indian state of Maharashtra. It is famous for the main temple of Lord Khandoba. It is a famous temple town being the family deity of many houses in Maharashtra and Karnataka. Its economy is centered on businesses catering to the numerous devotees coming to worship the Khandoba Temple there. Recently the increase in property rates and the planning of an international airport near the town has seen a spurt of development happening there.</string>
    <string name="jain_desc">Peace and tranquillity are the two most dominant forces at this prominent place of worship, Katraj Jain Temple. The temple sits on a hillock which lies between the Pune-Satara highway, at Katraj in the district of Pune, Maharashtra. The mesmerizing view from the temple of the Pune city adds to the feeling of calmness experienced by the visitors. Once the temple is entered, there is no stopping the refreshing breeze from blowing into your hair. The temple is appreciated for its beauty, calmness and the significance it holds towards Jainism and ancient Jainism literature. The temple is not too old as it was built in the 20th century. Its other name famous among the locals is ‘Aagam Mandir’.</string>
    <string name="dehu_desc">With an imposing statue of Sant Tukaram Maharaj, Dehu Gatha is known for being one of the biggest temples in Pune. The wonderful statue greets the visitors at the entrance of the temple and this place makes for a memorable visit in Pune. One of the most notable sights at Dehu Gatha is the various carvings from all the Gathas on Sant Tukaram embellished on the walls of this temple. It is often said that tourists who visit the temple must read at least 3 Gathas.</string>
    <string name="par_desc">Amongst the most famous ‘tekdis’ and hillocks in the town of Pune, Maharashtra, Parvati Hill offers visitors gorgeous and stunning views of the surrounding valley. With a history dating back to almost 250 years, Parvati Hill is famous for its temples and museums, in addition to being one of the oldest structures in Pune.Built in the early mid-17th century, the Parvati Hill Temple Complex can be found on Parvati Hill. The temple is located at the top of the hill and enshrines the idols of Lord Ganesha, Goddess Parvati, Lord Vishnu, Lord Karthikeya as well as Devateshwar. It is also said to have served as the sole place of worship of the Peshwa rulers in the bygone eras.</string>
    <string name="san_desc">Sangameshwar temple near to sasvad, at the confluence of the Karha and the Chamli rivers, is believed to have been built sometime around the 7th-10th century during the Yadava reign. The temple retains the old-look which adds to its charm. Renovations are good, but if they change the look or the architectural style of the original, it is as good as a new structure.</string>
    <string name="mor_desc">Morgaon Ganpati Temple is a famous pilgrimage destination and is dedicated to Lord Ganesha. It is located in Moragaon near Pune in the state of Maharashtra. It operates under the administration of the Chinchwad Devasthan Trust. Check Check, latest Morgaon Temple Timings and Rituals informationShri Moreshwar Ganpati temple or Shri Mayureshwar Ganpati temple of Morgaon has great importance among the Ashtavinayak (pilgrimage of eight Ganesha temples) temples of Maharashtra. In fact, Morgaon Mayureshwar Ganpati Temple is one of the most popular Ashtavinayak temples. This small and beautiful temple is located on the bank of river Karha in Baramati Taluka of Pune district</string>

    <!--Temple Time-->
    //Dagadu
    <string name="dagadu_1">1.Suprabhatam Aarti – 07:30 AM to 07:45 AM</string>
    <string name="dagadu_2">2.Naivedyam – 01:30 PM to 01:45 PM</string>
    <string name="dagadu_3">3.Madhyana Aarti – 03:00 PM to 03:15 PM</string>
    <string name="dagadu_4">4.Mahamangal Aarti – 08:00 PM to 09:00 PM</string>
    <string name="dagadu_5">5.Shejarti – 10:30 PM to 10:45 PM</string>

    //Aalandi Temple
    <string name="aalandi">1.Ringing:- 4 am</string>
    <string name="aalandi_1">2.Kakada Aarti:- 4 am to 4:15 am</string>
    <string name="aalandi_2">3.Pavaman Pooja :- 4:15 am to 5:30 am</string>
    <string name="aalandi_3">4.Mahimna Pooja:- 6 am to 7 am</string>
    <string name="aalandi_4">5.Open for darshan:- 5:30 am to 12:30 p.m.</string>

    //Bhimashankar Temple
    <string name="bhim_1">1.Mandir opening time	:-4.30 am</string>
    <string name="bhim_2">2.Morning Aarti:-4:45 am to 5.00 am</string>
    <string name="bhim_3">3.Nijarup darshan:-5:00 am to 5.30 am</string>
    <string name="bhim_4">4.Normal Darshans:-5:30 am to 2:30 pm</string>
    <string name="bhim_5">5.No Abhishekam between:-12:00 pm to 12:30 pm</string>
    <string name="bhim_6">6.Maha Puja:-2.00 pm. to 12.30 pm</string>

    //Chattushringi Temple
    <string name="chat_1">1.ABHISHEK,POOJA, VASTRA:-08:15 am 10:00 am</string>
    <string name="chat_2">2.MORNING AARTI:-10:00 am 10:15 am</string>
    <string name="chat_3">3.NAIVAIDYAM:-11:00 am 11:30 am</string>
    <string name="chat_4">4.EVENING AARTI:-08:00 pm 08:10 pm</string>

    //Jejuri Temple
    <string name="je_1">1.Opening hours:-5:00 am</string>
    <string name="je_2">2.Bhupali:-5:00 am – 6:30 am</string>
    <string name="je_3">3.Dharshan:-6:30 am – 12:00 pm</string>
    <string name="je_4">4.Pooja:-12:00 pm – 12:30 pm</string>
    <string name="je_5">5.Naivedya:-12:30 pm – 1:00 pm</string>

    //jain Temple
    <string name="jain_1">The temple is open from 6 am to 9 pm daily. The check-in and check-out time of the Dharamshala is 12 pm. The best time to visit is in the mornings and in the evenings.</string>

    //Dehu temple
    <string name="dehu_1">1.from 6:30 am to 10:30 am in the mornings</string>
    <string name="dehu_2">2.from 5:30 am to 8:30 pm in the evenings.</string>
    <string name="dehu_3">3.For Saturdays, pilgrims:-darshan at Sant Tukaram temple up till 9 pm</string>

    //Parvati temple
    <string name="par_1">1.Monday:-5:00 am – 8:00 pm</string>
    <string name="par_2">2.Tuesday:-5:00 am – 8:00 pm</string>
    <string name="par_3">3.Wedesday:-5:00 am – 8:00 pm</string>
    <string name="par_4">4.Thursday:-5:00 am – 8:00 pm</string>
    <string name="par_5">5.Friday:-5:00 am – 8:00 pm</string>
    <string name="par_6">6.Saturday:-5:00 am – 8:00 pm</string>
    <string name="par_7">7.Sunday:-5:00 am – 8:00 pm</string>

    //Sangameshwar
    <string name="san_1">1.Monday:-7:00 am – 7:00 pm</string>
    <string name="san_2">2.Tuesday:-7:00 am – 7:00 pm</string>
    <string name="san_3">3.Wedesday:-7:00 am – 7:00 pm</string>
    <string name="san_4">4.Thursday:-7:00 am – 7:00 pm</string>
    <string name="san_5">5.Friday:-7:00 am – 7:00 pm</string>
    <string name="san_6">6.Saturday:-7:00 am – 7:00 pm</string>
    <string name="san_7">7.Sunday:-7:00 am – 7:00 pm</string>

    //Moreshwar Temple
    <string name="mor_1">1.Waking up of great god:-5:00 A.M</string>
    <string name="mor_2">2.First Prakshalana Pooja:-5:30 A.M</string>
    <string name="mor_3">3.Panchopachara Pooja, Naivedya and Dhoopaarti:-7:00 A.M</string>
    <string name="mor_4">4.Maha Pooja, Mahanaivedya:-12:00 Noon</string>
    <string name="mor_5">5.Prakshalana Pooja:-3:00 P.M </string>
    <string name="mor_6">6.	Dhoopaarti, Aarti of the Avarana Deities1:-8:00 P.M</string>
    <string name="mor_7">7.Maha Aarti, Dhoop, Deep, Naivedya:-8.30 P.M </string>

    <!--How to reach-->
    //Dagadu
    <string name="dagadu_road">The Dagdusheth Halwai Ganpati temple is well-connected by road to all major cities including Mumbai. It is located on Shivaji road in Budhwar Peth in Pune. Distance from Mumbai to Dagdusheth Ganpati temple is 150 km and should take close to 2 hours 45 minutes to reach by road</string>
    <string name="dagadu_train">The closest railway station to Dagdusheth Ganpati temple is Shivajinagar which is located around 3 km from the temple. Several trains like the Deccan Express, Sinhagad Express and Sahyadri Express ply between Mumbai and Shivajinagar in Pune. It takes close to 3 hours and 40 minutes to reach Shivajinagar from Mumbai by train</string>
    <string name="dagadu_air">The nearest airport to Dagdusheth Halwai Ganpati temple is the Pune airport which is around 11 km from the temple. There are several flights to Pune from Mumbai and it takes just around 45 minutes to reach Pune from Mumbai by flight. There are several cabs available to travel from the airport to Dagdusheth Halwai Ganpati temple.</string>


    // Aalandi
    <string name="alan_train">The nearest station is Pune located 24 km away. Major cities of India are linked to the Pune station.</string>
    <string name="alan_raod">he Maharashtra Roadways runs buses to Alandi from major routes passing through nearly every city of Maharashtra.</string>
    <string name="alan_air">Pune is the nearest airport. One can hire a taxi or a cab from the airport to reach Alandi. </string>

    //Bhimashankar Temple
    <string name="bhim_car">The distance between Pune and Bhimashankar is 110.2 km and it can be covered in 2.5 to 3 hours, depending on the route you choose. There are 2 routes that one can choose from to reach Bhimashankar. For the shorter route, take Veer Santaji Ghorpade Road to Mumbai Highway in Juna Bazar. </string>
    <string name="bhim_bus">MSRTC operates buses between Pune and Bhimashankar. Buses are available every 30 minutes from 5:30 am to 4:00 pm.</string>

    //Chattushringi Temple
    <string name="chat_road">Buses are available everyday from Mumbai and also from nearby areas. Buses are also available from Satara, Raigad and Ahmednagar.</string>
    <string name="chat_rail">The nearest railway stations are Sivajinagar railway station, Khadki railway station, Dapodi railway station.</string>
    <string name="chat_air">The nearest airports to Chaturshringi Temple are Lohegaon Airport, Chhatrapati Shivaji International Airport, Gandhinagar Airport, Kolhapur Airport.</string>

    //Jejuri Temple
    <string name="je_road">Jejuri is very close to Pune City about 50 km from it.Of Pune, you can reach Jejuri by bus. There are several bus services operates to reach Jejuri.From Mumbai, you can reach Jejuri via Mumbai – Pune Expressway.From Aurangabad, you can arrive via Ahmednagar’s way.</string>
    <string name="je_rail">You can reach Jejuri through the railway station. From there Khandoba Temple is about 3 km. Pune is the next major railway station to the Jejuri</string>


    //jain Temple
    <string name="jain_reach">The nearest bus stops to the temple are ‘wonder city bus stop’ which is just 1.2 km away and the ‘Datta nagar bus stop’ which is just 1 km away from the temple. Many PMPML buses operate at these bus stops. You can find auto-rickshaws near-by the bus stops which will take you to the temple for a reasonable price. Private cars and cabs are also allowed to travel till the temple. The temple is 11.6 kms away from the Pune railway station and is 20.4 kms away from Pune airport.</string>

    //Dehu Temple
    <string name="dehu_bus">Buses frequently run between Swargate station and Dehu and so it is very easy to reach Dehu. Dehu lies at a distance of 25 km from Pune, and one can easily hire a cab or a bus from there to reach the temple.</string>

    //Parvati Temple
    <string name="par_air">The closest airport to Parvati Hill is the Pune International Airport, located around 16.8 kilometres away. In order to reach Parvati Hill from the airport, you need to reach the Swargate Bus Station, either by your own vehicles or by regular bus and taxi service from the airport. Public transportation will generally drop you off at the Bus station, after which you can take auto rickshaws to reach the hill.</string>

    //Moreshwar Temple
    <string name="mor_air">For tourists planning to visit this auspicious shrine by flight, Pune airport is the nearest destination, within 75 km.</string>
    <string name="mor_train">The Jejuri Railway Station located at 17 km from the temple is the nearest railway station.</string>
    <string name="mor_road">Special buses called Asthavinayaka darshan take tourists to all the eight temples. Buses to and from Pune are also available at the temple location itself.</string>


    <!--Pune Place Info-->

    //Description
    <string name="aga_desc">The mighty monument is an important part of Pune tourism and is also considered to be a sparkling jewel in Indian history which had a close connection with the Indian freedom movement since it served as a prison for Mahatma Gandhi and his wife, his secretary, and Sarojini Naidu. Kasturba Gandhi and Mahadev Desai, the secretary died in this palace.Archaeological Survey of India declared the palace as a monument of national importance in the year 2003. Aga Khan, the brilliant mind behind the birth of this majestic monument donated the palace to the Indian people as a mark of respect to Gandhi and his philosophy in 1969 and currently, the palace holds itself the vast collection of memories and it is a memorial on Gandhi where his ashes were kept.</string>
    <string name="osho_desc">Osho Ashram is one of the famous tourist places in Pune located in the Koregaon Park. The founder of the ashram was Rajneesh Chandra Mohan Jain who is famous among the people as Osho Rajneesh. The ashram has got another title as Osho Commune International of Pune and it is spread across 32 acres of land. Those who are eagerly waiting to escape into the laps of peace and tranquillity will fall in love with this ashram which is existing on a land of pure serenity and greenery and it offers the much-awaited break from the hustle and bustle of the city pollution and crowd. Currently, the ashram is perhaps the most visited tourist destination after it achieved fame among the tourists coming to Pune as well.</string>
    <string name="lal_desc">Lal Mahal is one of the famous tourist places in Pune which has another name as Red Palace. It is a beautiful monument established in 1630 AD by Shivaji Maharaj’s father Shahaji Bhosale for his wife and son. Shivaji Maharaj lived here for a long time until the time he captured his first fort.The original one had undergone several destructions and the current one is a reconstructed structure, located at the heart of the city. Shivaji’s wedding with Maharani Saibai took place in this palace.The original monument was constructed with the aim of rejuvenating the city of Pune when Dadoji Kondev entered the city with Shivaji Maharaj. The history recorded at various places proves the fact that Lal Mahal was used for organising feasts for the Brahmins during the thread ceremony of Sadoba, the son of Chimajiappa.</string>
    <string name="cafe_desc">How would you feel if a cafe gets blend with all the luxury you ever need? Interestingly, Paash is one such wonder near to your own door in the calm city of Pune. This organic cafe has the beauty of sustainable architecture along with a store of plush clothes, decorated artifacts, home-wares and gifts that you can take back for your family and friends.Dive in the beauty of white clad walls covered with picture frames, royal chandeliers, and make sure you do not miss out the events they love to host at this amazing visiting place in Pune. </string>
    <string name="Din_desc">An intriguing museum with a lot of references to the medieval history of India is located in Pune and that is the most famous tourist places in Pune, Raja Dinkar Kelkar Museum. It possesses the rare collection of Dr. Dinkar G Kelkar dedicated to the memory of his sone, Raja. There are three floors for this museum displaying different types of sculptures dating back to the 14th century along with ivory, silver and gold items and musical instruments, war weapons, vessels etc. The collection began in 1920 and by 1960, the museum was filled with 15000 objects and later in 1962, Dr. Kelkar donated all the collections to the Government of Maharashtra. Currently, if you visit the museum, you will come across more than 20000 objects out of which 2500 only are on display. </string>
    <string name="nda_desc">NDA is the sophisticated acronym of the National Defence Academy in Pune. It is the joint services academy of the Indian Armed Forces where three sections of the defence field such as the Army, the Navy and the Air Force cadets are trained together before the get pre commissioning training in the respective service academies and it is one of the famous places to visit in Pune city.The academy is located at Khadakwasla near Pune and it is the first tri service academy in the world. Since its establishment, the cadets from the academy have led and fought in major conflicts in which the Indian Armed Forces has been called to action. </string>
    <string name="friend_desc">Tucked away from the bustling city, lies a surreal place in Pune, Pune Okayama Friendship Garden that looks refreshingly green everywhere around as far as your eyes can see! Spread across 10 acres of land, This garden is inspired by a 300-year-old Japanese Korakuen garden that was developed by Ikeda Royal family in Okayama, Japan.his is the biggest Japanese garden in the world outside Japan and has also been featured in many Bollywood movies. The garden has become a key attraction in Pune and is also referred to as Pu. La. Deshpande Garden, in fond memory of Pu. La. Deshpande, a renowned Marathi writer.</string>
    <string name="rajiv_desc">Go for an amazing outing with your friends and family to Rajiv Gandhi Zoological Park when you are in the city of Pune. The famous park is known for having a snake park, an animal orphanage and a zoo that makes it totally worth a visit for lovers of wildlife and nature. Whether you are an adult or a kid, a visit to Rajiv Gandhi zoological park is an exciting trip to learn more about snakes and reptiles and come back with more knowledge about these elusive creatures.</string>
    <string name="taljai_desc">Maharashtra is blessed with a number of picturesque travel destinations that has a magnetic pull to nature lovers and adventure enthusiasts. Whether it is the verdant hills or dense forests, monsoon adds a mystical charm to these places when they look rejuvenated and green.Taljai Hills is a popular weekend getaway in the city of Pune, which is a favourite of tourists for its abounding natural beauty and exotic fauna. Tucked in the Western Ghats with a pleasant climate virtually round the year, the place has a number of attractions for environmentalists and shutterbugs. The open forest area provides a relaxing haven for morning and evening walks.</string>
    <string name="phule_desc">Founded in the year 1890, Mahatma Phule Museum is one of the must-visit Pune tourist attractions for history buffs. Earlier established as Lord Ray Museum, the museum was renamed as Mahatma Phule Museum in the year 1968. The museum makes for an interesting trip as one can see various collections of industrial products, agricultural items and handicraft pieces in this museum.Although the place has been about 118 years old now, it presents the old-world charm in the most amazing way to the tourists.</string>


    <!--Timing,Location,Fees-->

    //Agakhan Palace
    <string name="aga_time"> You can visit the palace on all days from 09:00 am to 05:30 pm.</string>
    <string name="aga_loc">Pune Nagar Road, Kalyani Nagar, Pune, Maharashtra 411014.</string>
    <string name="aga_fee"> For Indian nationals, the entry fee is INR 5, whereas for foreign nationals it is INR 100.</string>

    //Osho garden
    <string name="osho_time">The ashram is open on all days from 06:00 am to 10:30 pm.</string>
    <string name="osho_loc">17, Koregaon Park Road, Vasani Nagar, Koregaon Park, Pune, Maharashtra 411001.</string>
    <string name="osho_fee1">1.Rs.870 per person for Indians for 1 day and 2-day entry tickets</string>
    <string name="osho_fee2">2.Rs.1790 per person for foreigners for 1 day and 2-day entry tickets.</string>
    <string name="osho_fee3">3. 3day and 4-day tickets are discounted by 15% around.</string>
    <string name="osho_fee4">4.5 day entry tickets have discounts of 25% approximately and 30-day tickets will have a discount of about 40%.</string>


    //lal mahal
    <string name="lal_time">It is open on all days from 09:00 am to 01:00 pm and then from 04:00 pm to 08:00 pm.</string>
    <string name="lal_loc">Lal Mahal, Ganesh Rd, Durvankur Society, Kasba Peth, Pune, Maharashtra 411002.</string>
    <string name="lal_fee"> The entry fee to enter the palace is INR 3 per person.</string>

    //cafe paashh
    <string name="cafe_time">11.00 AM to 11.00 PM</string>
    <string name="cafe_loc">Kalyani Nagar, Pune</string>

    //dinkar Museum
    <string name="din_time">You can visit the museum round the year and it will be open from 10:00 am to 05:30 pm.</string>
    <string name="din_loc">1377_78, Natu Baug,Off. Bajirao Road,Shukrawar Peth, Pune, Maharashtra 411002.</string>
    <string name="din_fee1">1.Rs. 10.00 for children below 12 years</string>
    <string name="din_fee2">2.Rs. 50.00 for adult above 12 years</string>
    <string name="din_fee3">3.Rs. 200.00 for foreigners (adult)</string>
    <string name="din_fee4">4.Rs. 50.00 for foreigners (children)</string>
    <string name="din_fee5">5.Entry is free for blind and differently abled/ physically challenged visitors.</string>

    //NDA
    <string name="nda_time">The visit to the academy is restricted to Sundays only from 10:00 am to 12:30 pm.</string>
    <string name="nda_loc">NDA Alumni Association, National Defence Academy, PO NDA Khadakwasla, Pune-411023.</string>
    <string name="nda_fees">The entry to the academy is free of charge but you would need prior permission for the same. The application should be submitted a minimum 48 hours prior to the visit. Also, visitors should wear a formal dress in order to maintain the sanctity of the academy.</string>

    //friendship garden
    <string name="friend_time">6.30 AM - 10.30 AM and 4.00 PM - 8.00 PM Mon-Sun</string>
    <string name="friend_loc">Sinhgad Rd, Pune Okayama Friendship Garden, Dattawadi, Pune, Maharashtra </string>
    <string name="friend_fees">INR 5.00 for adults and children above 3 years. Children below 3 years have entry fees.</string>

    //Rajiv park
    <string name="rajiv_time">It can be visited by tourists between 9.30 and 5 pm</string>
    <string name="rajiv_loc">Satara Road, Near Bharati Vidyapeeth, Katraj, Pune, Maharashtra.</string>
    <string name="rajiv_feee">The entry fees for an adult is INR 15/ USD 0.23 and for the children, it is INR 5/ USD 0.07</string>

    //taljai hiils
    <string name="tal_time">Every day from 5AM- 10AM and 4:30PM -7PM</string>
    <string name="tal_loc">WaghJai Road, Taljai Forest Area, near Parvati, Pune, Maharashtra, India</string>
    <string name="tal_fee">There are no entry fees.</string>

    //Phule Museum
    <string name="phule_time">The timings are from 10:30 am to 5:30 pm. The museum remains closed on Wednesdays.</string>
    <string name="phule_fee">There is no entry fee to visit the museum</string>
    <string name="phule_loc">1204/10, Ghole Road, Shivajinagar, Pune, Maharashtra</string>

    <!-- PuneRestaurant-->
    //Description
    <string name="vaish_desc">A blog on city restaurants cannot go by without including Vaishali, one of the best veg restaurants in Pune. The place is a legend when it comes to serving authentic South Indian food that transports you instantly to the land of idli-sambar. Vaishali defies all logic when it comes to peak hour rush, as more often than not, you are likely to find a huge waiting line at the restaurant, even at 7 in the morning. For a Punekar, the place is a food Mecca and for the vast student community of the city, it is gods gift.  This decades-old restaurant has its own fan following, which swears by the taste and authenticity of its food.</string>
    <string name="german_desc">The Punekars swear by this cafe and those from overseas also throng it from morning to night. Off-late, the interiors of the good old bakery have been refurbished, but the essence of the place has stayed intact even after so many years of it serving lip-smacking delicacies. Leaving the bakery without getting their out-of-the-world Shrewsbury Biscuits packed, is almost considered a blasphemy in Pune. It is always full and you can spend the waiting time ogling at the sumptuous cakes and biscuits in the glass cabinets. German Bakery is almost a heritage spot for Punekars and it has continued to be their favorite</string>
    <string name="bounty_desc">A contribution to the Parsi-owned restaurant community of Pune, Bountys is another iconic name among sizzler lovers in Pune. The decor is minimal, but the efficient service and amazing food make up for this lacuna. For vegetarians, there is a wide assortment of dishes, both in the sizzlers section and on the main menu.</string>
    <string name="mala_desc">One of the best restaurants in Pune for dinner with your partner, Malaka Spice is sure to give you a great evening. The place is known for the creativity unleashed on the plates by their chef. With their Pan-Asian menu being reinvented every season, you will find an amazing array of fusion dishes from Thailand, Vietnam, Indonesia, and Burma. Malaka Spice is located at three locations in Pune, all three of which are a favorite of locals. Not only are the dishes innovative, but their names are also quite intriguing. All the dishes on the menu are classified into either of the two categories; A Chef Cheeru Original and Inspired not Imitated. You can select your sinful delight from the street food section or the Asian fusion section, both being equally exotic.</string>
    <string name="sen_desc">World cuisine at its best is what describes Sen5es. The interiors have been done in a modern style to make them comfortable. Sen5es is a favorite among the expats of Pune for its global cuisine. Diners can see their dishes being prepared through the open kitchen that overlooks the vast dining room. Interiors of Sen5es include glistening wooden floors paired with glass panels that lend it a classy look, supplemented by the feeling of warmth given out by the decorative fires.</string>


    <!--Location-->
    //vaishali
    <string name="va_loc"> Fergusson College Rd, Rage Path, Ganeshwadi, Shivajinagar, Pune, Maharashtra 411004</string>
    <string name="va_open"> 7:00 AM to 11:00 PM</string>
    <string name="va_miss1">1.SPDP (Sev Puri Dahi Puri)</string>
    <string name="va_miss2">2.Mysore Dosa</string>
    <string name="va_miss3">3.Sabudana Vada</string>
    <string name="va_miss4">4.Veg Cutlet</string>
    <string name="va_miss5">5.Filter Coffee</string>
    <string name="va_two">₹ 500 without alcohol</string>

    //german Bekary
    <string name="german_loc"> 292, N Main Rd, Ragvilas Society, Koregaon Park, Pune, Maharashtra 411001</string>
    <string name="german_open">7:45 AM to 11:45 PM</string>
    <string name="geman_miss1">1.Keema Pav</string>
    <string name="geman_miss2">2.Jerk Chicken</string>
    <string name="geman_miss3">3.Red Velvet Cake</string>
    <string name="geman_miss4">4.Mango Cheesecake</string>
    <string name="german_two">₹ 1100 </string>

    //Bounty
    <string name="bounty_loc"> Landmark Garden, Shop no 14,15 , 16, Rd Number 9, Kalyani Nagar, Pune, Maharashtra 411078</string>
    <string name="bounty_open1">12:00 PM to 4:00 PM</string>
    <string name="bounty_open2">7:00 PM to 11:30 PM</string>
    <string name="bount_miss1">1.Beef Sizzlers</string>
    <string name="bount_miss2">2.Paneer Steak Style</string>
    <string name="bount_miss3">3.Bbq Chicken</string>
    <string name="bount_miss4">4.Chicken Shashlik</string>
    <string name="bounty_two">₹ 1000 without alcohol</string>


    //Malaka Spice
    <string name="mala_loc">Siddharth Chambers, Lane, Off, N Main Rd, Koregaon Park, Pune, Maharashtra 411001</string>
    <string name="mala_opne">11:30 AM to 12:30 AM</string>
    <string name="mala_miss1">1.Three Aunties and Three Grandmothers</string>
    <string name="mala_miss2">2.Peranakan Spiced Chicken</string>
    <string name="mala_miss3">3.Lamb Chops</string>
    <string name="mala_miss4">4.Top Hats</string>
    <string name="mala_miss5">5.Lotus Stem Tango,</string>
    <string name="mala_miss6">6.Malay Grilled Chicken</string>
    <string name="mala_two">₹ 1500 without alcohol</string>

    //Sen5es

    <string name="sen_loc">81, Mundhwa Rd, Fatima Nagar, Koregaon Park Annexe, Mundhwa, Pune, Maharashtra 411001</string>
    <string name="sen_open">24 Hours</string>
    <string name="sen_miss1">1.Tomato and basil soup served in a rustic style</string>
    <string name="sen_miss2">2.Fresh Caesar Salad</string>
    <string name="sen_miss3">3.Fish and chips</string>
    <string name="sen_miss4">4.American T_bone steak</string>
    <string name="sen_two">₹ 2000 with alcohol</string>


    <!--Pune Malls-->
    <string name="amnora_desc">One of the most happening malls in Pune, Amanora Mall is a delight destination that promises fun, food, and you guessed it right, unlimited shopping! Located about 20 minutes away from Koregaon Park, the mall is built over 1.2 million sq. ft. It has two blocks, namely the East Block and West Block that await you with plush décor and an award-winning interior design. The Oasis, an open-air space with an exotic landscape is where people spend some quality time with their family and friends. The mall houses more than 150 stores that sell over 500 local and international brands, 50 outlets for food and beverage, a hypermarket, a multiplex by INOX, a fun gaming zone, and a plethora of options for buying home décor and electronic items. This is one of those places where you can have a gala time with your friends over weekends.</string>
    <string name="pheonix_desc">Touted to be one of the biggest malls in Pune, this famous chain of lifestyle malls has made its footprint in the city by blending in modern and traditional retail elements perfectly. The four-floored retailing paradise has a gigantic hypermarket, four spacious departmental stores, a value shopping bazaar, and over 280 retailing store partners. The stores include the right mix of premium and home labels for toys, books, electronics, beauty service and lifestyle stores, casuals, sports and luxury gear, art and craft, etc. For those who want to relax for a while after relentless shopping, the mall has a sprawling courtyard and a cascading waterfall area that is inspired by the great waterfalls near Pune. The kids’ play zone will keep your little ones engaged for hours on end.</string>
    <string name="pune_desc">Central Mall, Pune is meant for seasonal shoppers who binge-shop for affordable luxury brands. It houses a large departmental store for clothing, apparels, accessories, footwear, home décor, and lifestyle products. With over 300 brands to choose from at CMP, shoppers are bound to go bonkers over the variety of eclectic goods which are absolute trendsetters. The latest collection under each label is featured here for the fashion-forward people in town. The mall has a large food court to recharge at after a long day’s shopping spree with many fast-service counters and casual dining outlets. You do not have to worry about stationing your vehicles since the mall has a generous parking space. Venture into a world of uninterrupted shopping at Pune Central this weekend and gorge on some amazing grub afterward</string>
    <string name="ish_desc">This decadent mall is a representative of upbeat urban interiors and splendid architectural concepts. Ishanya hosts an eclectic collection of premier home décor and interior design brands selling the most inspirational merchandise. The food court and entertainment zones are no lesser, with a wide range of restaurants available at the venue, plus with the amphitheater, conference halls, party rooms, and more, there is something for everyone here. If you are planning to move to a new place, refurbish your home or simply take back some awesome furniture or home décor as a hobby, then Ishanya will never disappoint. Some of the stores at the mall such as @ Home, blueFROG, Home Town, Houslife, and Masper, among others, are enough to make furniture and home décor enthusiasts go crazy.</string>
    <string name="royal_desc">Decked up in a splendid Roman-inspired décor, this 25,000 sq. ft. of a dream mall is grand and enamoring. The mall has a host of events and activities for everyone. The amenities here include a ten-screen multiplex, a multi-storey departmental store, alfresco eateries, and luxury brand stores that reinvent retail concepts. The best of grocery shopping can be experienced here with local and imported products available on the racks.</string>

    //Amanora MAll
    <string name="amnora_loc">Mundhwa - Kharadi Rd, Amanora Park Town, Hadapsar, Pune, Maharashtra 411028</string>
    <string name="amnora_time">10.00 am to 10.00 pm; every day</string>
    <string name="amnora_bus">Bapusaheb Magarvasti </string>

    //Pheonix Mall
    <string name="pheonix_loc"> S No 207, Viman Nagar Road, Phoenix Road, Viman Nagar, Pune, Maharashtra 411014</string>
    <string name="pheonix_time">11.00 am to 11.00 pm every day (restaurants are open till 12.00 am)</string>
    <string name="pheonix_bus">Inorbit Mall Bus Stop</string>

    //Pune Central
    <string name="pune_loc">Pune Central, Karve Road MSM PARANJAPE MALL, Besides Garware College, Karve Rd, Pune, Maharashtra 411004</string>
    <string name="pune_time">11.00 am to 10.30 pm; every day</string>
    <string name="pune_stop">Garware College</string>

    //ishanya mall
    <string name="ish_loc">Shastrinagar, Yerawada, Pune, Maharashtra 411006</string>
    <string name="ish_time">11.00 am to 11.00 pm; every day/</string>
    <string name="ish_bus"> Ishanya Mall Bus Stop</string>

    //Royal Mall
    <string name="royal_loc">Dorabjee Paradise, NIBM Rd, Pune, Maharashtra 411060</string>
    <string name="roy_time">10.00 am to 11.00 pm; every day</string>
    <string name="royal_bus">Kad Nagar Chowk</string>


    <!-- Satara District-->
    <!-- Forts-->

    //Bhushangad fort
    <string name="bhu_desc">Bhushangad Fort built during the Devagiri Yadavas dynasty between 1210 – 1247 CE, it is one of the oldest such establishments in the region. The oval shape and a flat top design of the Fort make it stand out from the rest of the forts near Satara.Also, within the premises are two temples of - Maruti and Harini Devi, both of which can be explored during a visit. Besides that, one can also enjoy trekking and set camp at the Fort for a truly memorable experience.</string>
    <string name="bhu_loc">Bhushangad, Khatav Taluka, Satara District, Maharashtra 415538</string>
    <string name="bhu_dist">52.6 kilometres</string>
    //Kamalgad fort
    <string name="kama_desc">Situated at an elevation of 4511 feet above sea level, Kamalgad is a square-shaped hill fort which is among the prominent forts in Satara District. From its impressive height, visitors often savour views of the lush landscapes and the afar Dhoom Dam, for which they trek to the top.Furthermore, the history of this fort’s builder or commissioner is unknown. But the Kamalgad Fort was among one of the many others that were a part of the Bijapur ruling, which was later in 1818 seized by the British army to use as an execute site for war prisoner</string>
    <string name="kama_loc">Wai Taluka, Nandgane, Maharashtra 412803</string>
    <string name="kama_dist"> 64.5 kilometres</string>
    //Sajjangad Fort
    <string name="saj_desc">Situated in the mountainous area of the Western Ghats, Sajjangad is one of the best Forts in Satara District that is also a renowned pilgrimage site in India. Earlier named as Aashwalayangad, the fort was established by the Bahamani Emperors between 1347-1527 AD.The fort has a history of being conquered by several rulers, including Shivaji Maharaj who renamed it to Sajjangad. He also asked his spiritual gurus - Sri Ramdas to use it as an abode, which later became his resting place. Many in the present age visit here to pay respects to the idol, and enjoy many activities like picnic, camping and trekking.</string>
    <string name="saj_loc">Sajjangad Rd, Satara District, Gajawadi, Maharashtra 415013</string>
    <string name="saj_dist">16.9 kilometres</string>
    //Ajinkyatara Fort
    <string name="ajin_desc">Ajinkyatara means ‘Impregnable Star’ and doing full justice to its name, the Ajinkyatara Fort is one of the most important structures in shaping the history of Maharashtra. Situated at an elevation of 3300 feet of Ajinkyatara Peak, one of the seven mountains surrounding the city of Satara, this fort is where most tourists visit to enjoy a challenging trek and rewarding views of the entire city and the Sahyadri Hills.Built by Raja Bhoj of the Shilahara dynasty In 1673, there have been many changing rulers of the property over centuries, including the Mughals and Marathas.</string>
    <string name="ajin_loc">Satara, Maharashtra 415001</string>
    <string name="ajin_dist">3.9 kilometres</string>
    //Chandan Fort
    <string name="chan_desc">Situated on a hilly spur of the Sahyadri Range in Satara, Chandan - Vandana Fort was built by Bhoj II of the Shilahara dynasty in late 12th century. It is a set of two adjacent forts that are frequented by trekkers and ardent pilgrims.Both of these structures have admirable features and rather interesting history and have undergone ownership from dynasty to dynasty, including the Marathas and Mughals. Moreover, within the forts vicinity are demolished gates, bastions, a Lord Shiva Temple, a Mosque and many intact rooms worth exploring.</string>
    <string name="chan_loc">Banvadi, Satara District, Banwadi, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="chan_dist">23.4 kilometres</string>
    //Pandavgad Fort
    <string name="pan_desc">Pandavgad is another one of the hill forts in Satara District that spans over 6 acres of land. It is a square fortress that can be reached on foot by completing an arduous trek which gets too narrow in parts.Built in 1191-1192 AD by the Shilahar King Bhoj-II, the structure that remains today is mostly in ruins with only the temple and three of the six ponds accessible. Many come here not just for the history and the fort but also for the panorama of the village landscape and other adventures, such as camping.</string>
    <string name="pan_loc">Satara, Maharashtra 412803</string>
    <string name="pan_dist">46.8 kilometres</string>
    //Kenjalgad Fort
    <string name="ken_desc">This is one of the lesser-known forts near Satara that should be on your wishlist of offbeat experiences. The rhomboid-shaped fort is located at an elevation of 4269 feet, on the Mandhardevi spur of the Mahadev hill range in Wai.Kenjalgad was built during the 12th century by Bhoj Kings of Panhala, and like most other forts in the region was occupied by both Mughals and Marathas at different times. Today, the site is in ruins and mostly frequented by tourists and locals to enjoy treks and picnics with loved ones.</string>
    <string name="ken_loc">Mahadev hill range, Wai, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="ken_dist">64.5 kilometres</string>
    //Bhairavgad Fort
    <string name="bha_desc">Bhairavgad Fort is one of the best forts near Satara that have preserved a rich history and nature in its surroundings. Situated in the Kalsubai-Harishchandragad Wildlife Sanctuary of the Sahyadri Hills, this place is in ruins now and mostly interests adventurers and sightseeing enthusiasts.It is believed that the Fort and its components on the premises date back over 2500 years, so if you like history or architecture, you can take a tour of the innard temples and the compound.</string>
    <string name="bha_loc">Kalsubai-Harishchandragad Wildlife Sanctuary, Malsej Ghat, Akole taluka of Ahmednagar district, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="bha_dist"> 254 kilometres</string>
    //KalyangadFort
    <string name="kal_desc">Dominating the skyline with an impressive view of the Satara District, Kalyangad is another one of the Hill Forts near Satara frequented by travellers for a picnic, touring, treks and leisure. At an elevation of 3500 feet on a ridge of Nandgiri hill in the Mahadev range, this citadel is a strong example of great architecture and history with numerous temples, tombs and other elements present within.The construction of it dates back around 1178 AD to 1209 AD during the Shilahara dynasty rule. And much like the other forts, this too was ruled by Mughals, Marathas and the British.</string>
    <string name="kal_loc">Nandgiri hill, Satara District, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="kal_dist">23.6 kilometres</string>

    //Vasota Fort
    <string name="vas_desc">Situated in Bamnoli, a remote and naturally opulent area of the Satara District, Vasota Fort is among the most historically significant tourist attractions in the Western State of Maharashtra. Surrounded by diverse flora and fauna of the Sahyadri Hills.The forts near VAsota are famed trekking and camping sites which are visited by locals and other tourists. Speaking about the Fort’s history, it was built by Raja Nangopal of Panhala and remained under Maratha occupancy for the longest and later with the Shirkes and the Mores.</string>
    <string name="vas_loc">Bamnoli, Satara District, Maharashtra 415001</string>
    <string name="vas_dist"> 56 kilometres</string>

    <!--Temples-->
    //Kalubai temple
    <string name="kalu_desc">Mandhardevi Kalubai temple is near Wai (Satara District, Maharashtra, India). Located on a hill 4,650 feet above sea level, the temple, some 20 km from Satara, overlooks the picturesque Purandar fort. Devotees attribute miraculous properties to a grove around the shrine. Local lore has it that the temple is more than 400 years old and was built during Shivaji’s Maratha rule; no definite date on the construction is available.The title of the land is in the name of Lord Mandeshwar and Kaleshwari Devi. Most of the year there is little tourist traffic. The nearest primary health centre is six kilometres away and a major hospital is at Satara town.</string>
    <string name="kalu_time">6.00 AM and 9.00 PM.</string>
    <string name="kalu_reach">You can reach Kalubai Mandir Mandhardevi by taking MSRTC or Private Luxury Buses from Wai, Pune, and Satara. National Highway NH4 is the nearest National Highway to reach Kalubai Mandir Mandhardevi.</string>


    //Sangam Mauli Temple
    <string name="sangam_desc">Sangam Mahuli and Kshetra Mahuli are two villages that are located at the confluence of the Venna and the Krishna rivers in the Satara district of Maharashtra. Sangam translates to Confluence. Sangam Mahuli is a popular pilgrimage destination in Satara. It is famous for the 18th and 19th-century temples that boast a typical Maratha style of architecture. The village of Kshetra Mahuli is on the other side of River Krishna. It is believed to be the birthplace of Ramshastri Prabhune, a popular political and spiritual advisor of the Peshva period.</string>
    <string name="sangam_time">Though you can visit this place any time in any season , but be careful as in monsoon these rivers overflow and visiting this place is prohibited , one can also take a good view of these rivers from the flyover on satara – koregaon road.</string>
    <string name="sangam_reach">10 hr 24 min (509.7km)via NH60</string>
    //Chidabaram Nataraj temple
    <string name="chi_desc">The Nataraj Temple Chidambaram is also referred as Thillai Nataraj Temple. This temple is dedicated to Lord Shiva. It is in the southern state of Tamilnadu in India. The temple has a deep mythical connection. When the name of the town was Thillai, a Shiva shrine used to be there in the temple. Chidambaram is the name of the city where the temple is now situated literally meaning “clothed in thought” or “atmosphere of wisdom”.</string>
    <string name="chi_time1">Morning 6.00.a.m to 12.00 noon</string>
    <string name="chi_time2">Evening 5.00.p.m. to 10.00 night</string>
    <string name="chi_reach">State head quarters Chennai to Puducherry ( Pondycherry ) vila ECR or Chengalpattu Dindivanam, then Cuddalore, Chidambaram. Road : Road transport is very good in Cuddalore District. National highways NH45 , NH45A are running through Cuddalore.</string>

    //phutkey tale Ganapati temple
    <string name="phu_desc">As the name suggests, the presiding deity of the Phutke Tale Ganapathi temple is Lord Ganesha. Lord Ganesha is one of the prominent gods in Hindu mythology and revered by Hindus around the world. Ganapathi means lord of Ganas or lord of people. The elephant headed god is believed to remove any obstacle. The Hindu god of beginnings is evoked before every auspicious initiation. His vahana (Vehicle) is a rat symbolising his ability to overcome any obstacle.</string>
    <string name="phu_time">6:00 AM - 7:00 PM</string>
    <string name="phu_reach">It takes 2 hours, 32 minutes to travel from Shraddha Terraces to Phutke Tale Ganapati Temple. Approximate driving distance between Shraddha Terraces and Phutke Tale Ganapati Temple </string>
    //yavateshwar temple
    <string name="yav_desc">he temple is quite popular for tourists and visitors who visit nearby locations such as Pune, Mahabaleshwar, and Panchgani, etc. The temple is located in the village of Yewateshwar in Satara district of Maharashtra. It is 5km far from Satara city.This temple is surrounded by fresh, breezy, green and dense forests of Sahyadri Western Ghats. You can also visit Yewateshwar hill which is just nearby Yawateshwar temple. This temple is solely dedicated to Lord Shiva.</string>
    <string name="yav_time">7 AM to 7 PM</string>
    <string name="yav_reach">Satara is well connected to all nearby towns through buses, and frequent buse0s will be available to the towns and cities of Pune, Mumbai, Raigad, Khandala, Guhagar, Chiplun, Baramati, Mahabaleshwar and Panchgani. Both semi deluxe buses and deluxe buses will be available to Satara and important cities like Mumbai and Pune will even have air conditioned coaches that ply to Satara. Bus fares for the normal class of travel will range around Rs 150–200 from the nearby locations within the state.</string>

    <!--Dams-->
    //Dhoom dam
    <string name="dhoom_desc">	The Dhoom Dam is an earth fill and gravity dam build across the Krishna river near Wai. Its official name is Dhoom Dam D02958. The primary purpose of this dam was to Irrigation and generated Hydroelectricity. This dam generates 4MG electricity from the basement electricity house. The height of the dam is 50 meters, and the length is 2,478 meters.</string>
    <string name="dhoom_type">	Earthfill,Gravity</string>
    <string name="dhoom_cap">331,100 km3 (79,400 cu mi)</string>
    <string name="dhoom_area">	2,498 km2 (964 sq mi)</string>


    //Kanher Dam
    <string name="kan_desc">The Kanher Dam is an earth-fill and gravity dam build across the Wenna river near Satara. The primary purpose of this dam was to Irrigation and generated Hydroelectricity. The height of the dam is 50.34 meters, and the length is 1,954 meters.</string>
    <string name="kan_type">Earthfill,Gravity</string>
    <string name="kan_cap">271,680 km3 (65,180 cu mi)</string>
    <string name="kan_area">18.63 km2 (7.19 sq mi)</string>

    //Koyna Dam
    <string name="koyna_desc">The Koyna Dam is a Rubble-concrete dam build across the Koyna river near Koyna Nagar. Its official name is Koyna Dam D05104. The primary purpose of this dam was to Irrigation and generated Hydroelectricity. It is one of the largest dam in India. This dam is having a total installed capacity of 1,960 MW. The height of the dam is 103.2 meters, and the length is 807.2 meters.</string>
    <string name="koyna_type">	Rubble-concrete dam</string>
    <string name="koyna_cap">2,797,400,000 m3 (2,267,900 acre⋅ft)</string>
    <string name="koyna_area">	891.78 km2 (344 sq mi)</string>

    //Mhaswad Dam
    <string name="mhaswad_desc">The Mhaswad Dam is an earth-fill dam build across the Maan river near Maan. It’s also named Rajewadi Dam. The primary purpose of this dam was to Irrigation. The height of the dam is 24 meters, and the length is 2,473 meters.</string>
    <string name="mhaswad_type">Earthfill</string>
    <string name="mhaswad_cap">46,210 km3 (11,090 cu mi)</string>
    <string name="mhaswad_area">16,251 km2 (6,275 sq mi)</string>

    //Morana Dam
    <string name="morna_desc">The Morana Dam is an earth-fill dam build across the Morana river near Patan. It’s also named Gureghar Dam. The primary purpose of this dam was to Irrigation. The height of the dam is 47.02 meters, and the length is 420 meters.</string>
    <string name="morna_type">Earthfill</string>
    <string name="morna_cap">36,990 km3 (8,870 cu mi)</string>
    <string name="morna_area">31.27 km2 (12.07 sq mi)</string>


    <!--Solapur Info-->
    <!--Fort-->
    //Manchur Fort
    <string name="manchur_desc">There is a local tale linked to the naming of this fort. After capturing the village and nearby areas, Aurangzeb ordered his men to destroy the Shiv Linga but none of them succeeded due to a heavy attack of bees. Furious Aurangzeb later sent beef covered in a cloth as an offering to the Shiv linga as a measure of insult and disrespect. When the cloth was removed the beef turned into white flowers. That’s why it became Maas-Noor and later Machnur. Deeply ashamed by this act Aurangzeb started annually two donations of Rs.400 and Rs.6. Even today the Government of Maharashtra gives an annual donation of Rs.480 to the temple.</string>
    <string name="manchur_visit">The fort is still in well built condition. There are porches on two sides of the wall on entering the main door and a Mosque to its opposite side. There a water tank carved in stone in front of the Mosque and to its back is the deep basin of Bhima river. The fortification alongside the river has been devastated due to flooding of the river.</string>
    <string name="manchur_reach">Machnur village is 43 kms from Solapur and 21 kms from Pandharpur on Solapur – Pandharpur road, while its 12 kms from Mangalvedhe. The road in the village which takes us to the temple complex first further leads to the fort where the road ends.</string>
    //Mangalwedha Fort
    <string name="mang_desc">Mangalwedha is approximately 50 km. southwest of the city of Solapur, and 25 km southeast of Pandharpur.Known for being the birthplace of Sri Jayatirtha, the great Dvaita saint and commentator on Sri Madhvacarya’s works, Mangalwedha is also home to an ancient Brahma Temple.</string>
    <string name="mang_visit">The current structure of the fort is a small miniature fort type with four bastions and houses the office of Divisional Magistrate.The trench of the fort is now devastated. At the corner we can find some sculptures and idols of Gods and Goddesses.The present ruined state of the fort hints that the fort must have been huge in the earlier times.</string>
    <string name="mang_reach">Mangalwedha is 50 kms from the District city of Solapur and 23 kms from the holy town of Pandharpur and buses are easily available.</string>
    //Piliv Fort
    <string name="piliv_visit">There are bastions on four corners of the fort and there are narrow windows (Jangyas) in the bastions and the fort wall. After entering from the main door one can find porches built in the door way for the gatekeepers. There is a structure opposite to the main entrance which is in a dilapidated condition. Within this structure on the right corner there is a room which is built below the bastion and has enclosed balconies which is supposed to be used for watch keeping purpose.</string>
    <string name="piliv_desc">Piliv fort is a small fort situated on the slope of Piliv village of Solapur, Maharashtra. It is a hill fort and base village is Piliv.</string>
    <string name="piliv_reach">From Pune there are ST (State Transport) buses / Volvo buses available to Pandharpur, which is around 207 kms from Pune, from Pandharpur there are buses available to Piliv village, which is 48 kms from Dahiwadi.</string>
    //Karmala Fort
    <string name="karmala_desc">Encircled by a strong wall and a moat, the fort comprises twenty-one bastions, the expanse between them being some hundred or more feet. The Karmala fort is situated around 12 miles from the Jeur railway station, which again is 82 miles away from the Solapur railway junction, the biggest one in the region.</string>
    <string name="karmala_visit">There are two principal gates for entry into the fort. One gate is on the eastern side, and the other is on the opposite side. Temples of Maruti, Brahma, Vishnu and Mahesha as also of Mahadeo have been erected in front of the main gate of the fort. The building immediately behind these temples once served as the residence of Rao Rambha Nimbalkar. However it has now been converted to a civil court. It also serves as the office for the area.</string>
    <string name="karmala_reach">Reach Solapur first before heading to the fort, which is very close to the city. The city is well connected with the rest of the country by train, air and buses.</string>
    //Dhotri Fort
    <string name="dhotri_desc">Gadhi is located in Dhotri village. The fort is in a good condition and its main attraction is the spiral stairway built in the bastion.The fort is surrounded by the village on one side and loose soil on the other.The fort is surrounded by the village on one side and loose soil on the other. A certain part of it has been collapsed but the pattern is untouched. The same kind of stone is used to build houses of the locals around the fort.</string>
    <string name="dhotri_visit">There are four bastions to the fort and the bastion to the south has a spiral stairway leading to the top which gives a complete view of the fort and its structure. After descending the bastion one comes across a room built in the fortified wall with a semi circle shaped roof. Moving ahead parallel to the fort wall one can see the remnants of the structure on the way to the West bastion. Here there is a small doorway covered in bushes which takes us to the rectangular open ground with fort wall on all sides and two bastions on its two corners. There is a dried up well to the right.</string>
    <string name="dhotri_reach">Kardehalli village is 19 kms from Solapur on the Solapur-Akkalkot road. Take the small road road to the left of the main road. Dhotri fort is 14 kms from Kardehalli.Bramhani village is 15 kms from Solapur on the Solapur-Hyderabad highway. A small road to the right of a main road takes us to Dhotri village which is 24 kms via Musali-Tandulwadi.</string>

    <!-- temples-->
    //Siddheshwar Temple

    <string name="sid_hist">As per the records, Siddheshwar temple was built by a yogi, and a devotee of Shri Mallikarjuna of Srisailam, Shri Siddharameshwar. He built this temple and made 68 Shiva lingams in the temple as per the instructions of his guru. It is said that Shri Siddheshwar, who is also considered as the six prophets of Lingayat religion, believed that birth of this saint caused the prosperity of the city and the deity is capable of blessing the devotees.</string>
    <string name="sid_reach">The temple, hardly 2 kilometers from the main railway station, is easily accessible by local means of transport, be it bus or auto.</string>
    <string name="sid_time">07:00 AM to 08:00 PM, Open all days</string>
    //Rupabhavani Temple
    <string name="rupa_hist">The temple was built by Bandoba Pawar, a great devotee of Rupa Bhavani who was blessed by the Goddess while ploughing a field. The idol of the Goddess is said to have emerged from the field when his plough got stuck at the very spot the temple has been built. Tuesdays and Fridays are the days of the week when a Mahapuja is performed for the Goddess. The Temple features ancient architecture with engravings depicting stories from Puranas.</string>
    <string name="rupa_time">9:00 AM - 7:00 PM</string>
    <string name="rupa_reach">4 kms From the city center</string>
    //Dwarkadhish Temple
    <string name="dwa_hist">Dwarka, the Kingdom of Lord Krishna is a wonder in itself; it is the land of legends and myths. Dwarka has a charm that touches our heart and a history which takes us to medieval times. This holy city on the banks of Gomti River is one-of-its-kind place. Legend says, Lord Krishna left Mathura and created a new kingdom of his own named DwarkaRead more at: https://www.nativeplanet.com/travel-guide/dwarkadhish-temple-in-dwarka-002907.html</string>
    <string name="dwa_reach">Dwarka is located in Devbhoomi Dwarka District. It is around 128km from Jamnagar in Gujarat. It is well-connected by road through other parts of Gujarat. Dwarka is around 444km from Ahmedabad.</string>
    <string name="dwa_time1">Morning 6:30AM to Afternoon 1:00PM</string>
    <string name="dwa_time2">Evening 5.00 to 9.30 Morning Timings</string>


    //Shri Swami Samarth Temple
    <string name="shri_desc">Akkalkot is a Holy place of Shri.Swami Samarth Maharaj. It is located at a distance of 38 kms. by road from Solapur District headquarters. This Saint is believed to be the reincarnation of Lord Dattatraya. The Samadhi of this Saint is worshipped by the devotees. The Death Anniversary is celebrated on Chaitra Shuddha Trayodashi every year. Large number of devotees visit the place everyday.</string>
    <string name="shri_time"> Everday 6am to 8pm </string>
    <string name="shri_reach">Akkalkot is 40 kms from Solapur. kkalkot road railway station is about 11 kms from Akkalkot city. This station falls on the Solapur-Wadi route of central Railway.</string>
    //Shri Ambabai temple in Tuljapur
    <string name="amba_desc">Tuljapur, the one amongst three and half Shakti Peethas (abodes of cosmic powers) of the state, is situated in Maharashtra, wherein resides the Mother Goddess Tulja Bhavani. She is also fondly revered as Aai (mother) Ambabai, Jagdamba, Tukai by her devotees who throng in millions to Tuljapur for her Darshan and for seeking her blessings. As a divine Mother, she protects her children from the sins of evil desires, selfishness, jealousy, hatred, anger and ego. At the same time, TuljaBhavani symbolizes the power of the Supreme Being that maintains moral order and righteousness in the universe.</string>
    <string name="amba_reach">22.4 Km away from district headquarter Osmanabad  and 77.0 Km from Latur.</string>
    <string name="amba_time">4am to 10 pm , Sunday Closed</string>


    <!--Dams-->
    //Ashti Dam
    <string name="ashti_spec">The Ashti Dam is an earth-fill dam build across the Ashti river near Mohol. The primary purpose of this dam was to Irrigation. The height of the dam is 17.6 meters, and the length is 3,871 meters.</string>
    <string name="ashti_co">17.8002707°N 75.4275261°E</string>
    <string name="ashti_cap">23,000 km3 (5,500 cu mi)</string>
    <string name="ashti_impound">Ashti river</string>
    //Babhulgaon Dam
    <string name="babhul_spec">The Babhulgaon Dam is an earth-fill dam build across the local river near Barshi. The primary purpose of this dam was to Irrigation. The height of the dam is 16.93 meters, and the length is 16.5 meters.</string>
    <string name="babhul_co">18.3214476°N 75.7810307°E</string>
    <string name="babul_cap"> 56,100,000 km3 (13,500,000 cu mi).</string>
    <string name="babul_impound">local river</string>
    //Bhudihal Dam
    <string name="bhu_spec">The Bhudihal Dam is an earth-fill dam build across the Belwan river near Sangola. Its official name is Bhudihal Dam D03459. The primary purpose of this dam was to Irrigation. The height of the dam is 18.5 meters, and the length is 2,975 meters.</string>
    <string name="bhu_co">18°04′26″N 75°07′12″E</string>
    <string name="bhu_cap">0.027950 km3 (0.006706 cu mi)</string>
    <string name="bhu_impound">	Belwan river</string>
    //Ekrukh Dam
    <string name="ek_spec">The Ekrukh Dam is an earth-fill dam build across the Adela river near Solapur. Its official name is Ekrukh dam D00981. The primary purpose of this dam was to Irrigation and Water Supply. The height of the dam is 21.45 meters, and the length is 2,360 meters.</string>
    <string name="ek_co">17.7402569°N 75.9149802°E</string>
    <string name="ek_cap">61,170 km3 (14,680 cu mi)</string>
    <string name="ek_impound">	Adela river</string>
    // Hingani Dam
    <string name="hi_spec">The Hingani Dam is an earth-fill dam build across the Bhogawati river near Barshi. Its official name is Hingani Dam D01362. It’s also named Pangaon Dam. The primary purpose of this dam was to Irrigation. The height of the dam is 21.87 meters, and the length is 2,193 meters.</string>
    <string name="hi_co">18.1347177°N 75.8366489°E</string>
    <string name="hi_cap">31,970 km3 (7,670 cu mi)</string>
    <string name="hi_impound">	Bhogawati river</string>


    <!-- Kolhapur Info-->
    <!--Forts-->
    //Rangana
    <string name="rang_hist">This fort was built by the King Bhoj-II of the Shilahar dynasty in 12 th century.[2] In 1470 this fort was captured by Md. Gavan of Bahamani dynasty. Later it was under the control of Sawant rulers of Adilshahi dyanasty. In 1658 the Rustum Jaman, commander-in chief of Adilshah won it from the Sawants. Jijabai undertook a special drive and captured the fort on 15.8.1666. This fort was under the control of Karvir kings for a longer period until the British took control in 1818.[3] In December 1664 by a series of surprise attacks Shivaji Maharaj defeated the combined forces of Bijapur and the Desais and captured the Rangna Fort. Lakham Sawant and the Desais fled to Portuguese territory</string>
    <string name="rang_reach">There is a good motorable road up to the base village Patgaon. It takes about two hour to reach the fort.An hour\'s journey from Narul Village Kudal to Rangana Fort for walking. Shivaji Maharaj used this way to go rangana fort from kokan. For trakking persons can be used walkway from Gothos, Nileli, Narul Villages</string>
    <string name="rang_place">There is a pilgrimage ashram of Mouni Maharaj on the way from Patgaon village. In the year 1676 Shivaji Maharaj took blessings from the Maharaj before proceeding for the Southern conquest. After walking for few steps there is an old Bhadrakali temple. There are two gates, a large lake and temple of goddess Ranganai devi on the fort.</string>

    //Mansantosh
    <string name="man_hist">It is believed that this fort was built or repaired by Shivaji. Shivaji entered this area on 11 April 1667 to lift the siege of Rangana fort. After lifting the siege of Rangana fort, he arrived to this fort on 13 May 1667. He stayed here for 34 days till June 15, 1667.Later, the control of Manohar-Mansantosh fort passed to the Chhatrapati of Kolhapur. In 1834, the fort garrison (gadkar) revolted against the Chatrapati which was again demolished by sending a chieftain. later due to regular cases of mutiny, Ch. Shahaji Maharaj (Buwa Maharaj) himself captured the fort on1936, it is recorded that he arrested the culprits and took back 2 guns from the fort. After the death of Ch. Shahaji Maharaj (Buwa Maharaj) in 1838, the gadkars again revolted against the fort, The then Chhatrapati sent his chiefs to break it, he suppressed the rebellion and gave asylum to the rebels.</string>
    <string name="man_reach">The nearest town is Kudal and Sawantwadi. The base village of the fort is Shivapur, but there is a motorable road up to Gadkarwadi. From Bhairav mandir it will take 45 minutes almost to climb. There are good hotels at kudal and Sawantwadi. Sawantwadi and Kudal both are well connected rail to Mumbai and Goa.The trek route passes through dense forest and the ascent is very steep. It requires about 1 hour to reach the scarp. There are dialapedeted rock cut steps to climb the scarp. The night stay on the fort is not possible.</string>
    <string name="man_place">The manohargad is triangular in shape and larger in size than Mansantoshgad.It is 15 acres in size.The fort walls are in demolished condition .There is a well, entrance gate and few buildings in ruined condition on the fort</string>

    //Gandharvagad
    <string name="gan_hist">Gandharvagada is mentioned in the list of forts built by Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj. This fort was built during the Shiva period. In 1844, the British wreaked havoc on a large scale.</string>
    <string name="gan_reach">Kolhapur, Nipani, Gadhinglaj to Chandgad. On the way from Kolhapur to Chandgad, 10 km from Chandgad. In the distance is the fork of Wahkuli village. An arch is currently erected on this fork, which bursts to the left of the road. The road leading to Gandharvagada is made from this fork. This road leads to the sandy village in the foothills of the fort. You can reach the fort in just fifteen minutes walk from the village or you can reach the top by taking a detour by car. From Walkuli village we climb Gandharvagad.</string>
    <string name="gan_place">We enter the fort through the broken ramparts. Two or three towers can be seen standing on the sloping ramparts on this side. There is a loophole in this rampart but it is completely extinguished due to the cracks. There is a small well ten feet deep near the ramparts. The bottom of the well seemed to be leaking in one corner. Chaloba on Gandharvagada is the village deity and place of worship of the people of the village. The villagers have completely transformed this old small temple and built a new big temple. The temple has a chaloba mask</string>

    //Samangad
    <string name="sam_hist">Like other forts in Kolhapur district, the credit for building the fort goes to Shilahar Raja Bhoj II. In the year 1667, Shivaraya conquered this fort. The fort was fortified by Asab Pradhan Mandal\'s wealthy Assamese and South Subha chief Surnis Annaji Dutto. Annaji Dutto Prabhunikar has played an important role in the reconstruction of Samangad. They had the subconscious of this part. In 1688, the fort was conquered by the Mughals. Before the year 1701, this fort came back to the Marathas. Prince Bedarbakht laid siege to the fort and conquered it, and Shahamir appointed him fort keeper. In the year 1704, the Marathas recaptured it. After this the ruler of this fort was Karveerkar Chhatrapati. In 1844, Saman Gad raised the flag of the first rebellion against the British.</string>
    <string name="sam_reach">If you have your own vehicle, you can reach Bhadgaon Chennakupi via Gad Hinglaj. Chinchwadi and then Samangad can be reached via Chennakupi.</string>
    <string name="sam_place">From Gadhinglaj via Bhadgaon Chinchewadi we used to set foot on the fort plateau. The two firearms next to the big well in Chinchewadi village testify to the historicity of the village. The left hand asphalt road leads to the fort. The road on the right hand side leads to Maruti Mandir. You used to enter the fort on the left hand side road. This place used to have a door, but it has become extinct over time. On all sides of Samangad, Katal is drawn. It is fortified with towers.</string>
    //Bhairavgad
    <string name="bhai_hist">The main aim to build this fort was to keep an eye on the Tolarkhind route of Harishchandragad fort. The route to approach Tolarkhind is from Khireshwar village in Pune district and Kothale village in Nagar district. The architecture of this fort indicates that it must have been built in the same era as Harishchandragad fort.The mountain range start from Kothale village where at first there is a hill with the shape of a Shivlinga. This hill is named as Kolatha. Next to it there is a peak after which there is Bhairavgad with a flat surface and another peak named “Gadhavacha Dongar” which literally means Donkey’s hill. All these peaks are visible from Kothale village.Lord Bhairoba on the fort is the local deity. Villagers go barefoot from the second ladder on the fort. Every year in the Hindu month of Chaitra a religious procession is conducted here.</string>
    <string name="bhai_reach">Reach Otur village from Mumbai – Kalyan – Murbad – Malshej ghat. A road passing alongside Otur S.T. bus stand goes to Kothale village via Bamanwada – Kotul (30 kms) – Vihir (base village of Kunjargad fort) – Kotul (25 kms). Total distance 214 kms.</string>
    <string name="bhai_place">The summit of the fort is small. After we enter the fort there is the place of Lord Bhairav on the right to the north. There are some sculptures and Veerghals next to it. In front of it there are two rock cut water tanks and two lamp posts behind them. Behind the Lord Bhairav’s place railings are installed from where one can see Harishchandragad fort, Taramati peak and its Vetaldhar. After visiting Lord Bhairav’s place proceed to the opposite direction (South) where one can see a mountain taller than Bhairavgad. This is “Gadhavacha Dongar”. It is believed that Bhairavgad is the Lord’s Chariot and the Gadhavacha Dongar is a Donkey pulling the Chariot. While proceeding towards this mountain we come across five water tanks. It takes 30 minutes to visit the fort. From the fort top one can see Harishchandragad fort to the west, Bhairavgad (Shirpunje) to the north and Kunjargad to the east.</string>

    <!--Temples-->
    //Mahalakshmi Temple
    <string name="mahala_desc">The temple of the goddess Mahalakshmi was built by karndeva in 634 C.E Chalukya reign. Mounted on a stone platform, the murti of the crowned goddess is made of gemstone and weighs about 40 kilograms. The image of Mahalakshmi carved in black stone is 3 feet in height. The Shri Yantra is carved on one of the walls in the temple. A stone lion (the vahana of the goddess), stands behind the statue. The crown contains an image of the Vasuki. The temple is a Śāktaḥ Shrine dedicated to Mahalakshmi who is the presiding goddess of Pradhanik Rahasyam of Devi Mahatmya.Further it is known that Ambabai carries a Shivalinga atop her head (beneath the decorative crown), holds a Matulinga, a Mace, a Shield and a Drinking Bowl. This is also the description mentioned in the Rahasya of Devi Mahatmy[4]a. Unlike most Hindu sacred images, which face north or east, the deity faces West (Pashchim). There is a small open window on the western wall, through which the light of the setting sun falls on the face of the image for three days around the 21st of each March and September.There are a number of other shrines in the courtyard to the Navagrahas, Surya, Mahishasuramardini, Vitthal-Rukmini, Shiva, Vishnu, Bhavani and others. Some of these images date back to the 11th century, while some are of recent origin. Also located in the courtyard is the temple tank "Manikarnika Kund", on whose bank is another shrine to Visweshwar Mahadev.</string>
    <string name="mahala_hist">In 109 A.D, Karnadeo cut off the jungle and brought the temple to light. The existence goes back to the 8th century, according to Dr. Bhandarkar and Mr. Khare.[who?] In the 8th century, the temple sank down due to earthquake. In the 9th century, Gandavadix (King) extended the temple by building Mahakali Mandir. During 1178–1209, in the reign of Raja Jaysing and Sindhava, South gate and Atibaleshwar Temple were built. In 1218, Yadav king Tolum built Mahadwar, and offered jewels to Devi. Further, Shilaharas built Maha Sarasvati Mandir. He being a Jain, got 64 idols carved. It is possible that new idol called Padmavati was installed at that time.[according to whom?] Further, in Chalukya times, Ganapati before the temple was installed. In the 13th century, Shankaracharya built Nagar Khana and Office, Deepmalas.</string>
    <string name="mahala_fest">Kirnotsav (lit. festival of Sun Rays) is celebrated in the Mahalakshmi Temple at Kolhapur, when the rays of the sun fall directly on the deity at the time of sunrise. It is said that the Sun god pays his homage to Mahalakshmi Ambabai for three days in a year. In January the Sun is in the sign of Capricorn (Shravana nakshatra) transiting between 17,18, and 19th degree; while in November Sun transits through the 24, 25, and 26th degree in the sign of Libra (Vishaka nakshatra). This is not aligned to any specific tithis, since Lunar Calendar needs adjusting every few years and every year aligns to different Tithi. It is also not aligned to Uttarayan/ Daskshinayan of Suns movement since it is 9 months apart.</string>
    <string name="mahala_time">4:30 a.m to 10:00 p.m</string>

    //Jyotiba Temple
    <string name="joti_desc">Jyotiba Temple (Marathi: ज्योतिबा) is a holy site of Hinduism near Wadi Ratnagiri [1] in Kolhapur district of Maharashtra state in western India. The deity of the temple is known by the same name. An annual fair takes place on the full moon night of the Hindu months of Chaitra and Vaishakha.</string>
    <string name="joti_fest">Legend says that the god Jyotiba destroyed the evil Ratnasur. Jyotiba helped Ambabai in her fight with the demons. He founded his kingdom on this mountain, and belongs to the Nath sampradaya. Lord Jyotiba destroyed Raktabhoj Rakshasa, and Ratnasur Rakshasa thus liberating the region from its tyranny. The idol of Lord Jyotiba is four-armed.</string>
    <string name="joti_time">5:30 am to 10:30 pm</string>
    <string name="joti_hist">There was a small temple in the place of today’s Jyotiba’s big temple. The original temple is built by the devotee named Naavji from village kival near Karad. In 1730, Maharaja Ranoji Shinde of Gwalior renovated the original place in a grand place. This temple is simple and has been constructed with fine black basalt stone.</string>
    //Bhavani Mandap
    <string name="bhavani_desc">Bhavani Mandap is a historical building situated in the walled city center of Kolhapur in southern Maharashtra, India. It is located near the famous and mammoth Mahalaxmi Temple on the west.</string>
    <string name="bhavani_hist">Bhavani Mandap was an important meeting venue in yesteryears. It housed the offices of various court officials and was centre of many celebrations. It also saw a famous murder in the central courtyard. The place has the nostalgic charm and typical architecture of the British Raj bringing back memories of the rich princely state Kolhapur used to be.</string>
    <string name="bhavani_fest">Kiran Utsva — Navratri are the main festivals at Mahalaxmi temple Kolhapur.ny bolnar </string>
    <string name="bhavani_time">It is open throughout the day, all days of the week.</string>

    //Kopeshwar Temple
    <string name="kop_desc">Kopeshwar Temple is at Khidrapur, Kolhapur district, Maharashtra. It is at the border of Maharashtra and Karnataka.It is also accessible from Sangli as well. It was built in the 12th century by Shilahara king Gandaraditya between 1109 and 1178 CE. It is to the east of Kolhapur, ancient  and artistic on the bank of the Krishna river.Even though Shilahars were Jain kings, they built and renovated various Hindu temples, thus depicting their respect and love for all religions.</string>
    <string name="kop_hist">Apart from the legend, the name might have originated from the ancient name of the town, which was "Koppam". The town witnessed two major battles. The first one took place in 1058 CE between Chalukya king Ahavamalla and Chola king Rajendra. The Chola king Rajadhiraja was killed during the battle, and coronation of second king, Rajendra Chola took place right on the battlefield.The second battle took place between Shilahara king Bhoj-II and Devagiri Yadav king Singhan-II, during which king Bhoj-II was captured by Yadavas and was kept captive on the fort of Panhala. This event is recorded in the 1213 CE inscription near the south entrance of the temple. This battle brought rule of Kolhapur branch of Shilaharas to end</string>
    <string name="kop_time"> 7:00 am to 11:30 am and 4:00 pm to 8:00 pm</string>
    //Narsobawadi Temple
    <string name="nar_desc">Narasimhawadi commonly known as Narsobawadi or Narsobachi Wadi is a small town in Shirol Tahasil in Kolhapur district, Maharashtra. Narsobawadi gets its name from the presence of Shri Narasimha Saraswati, the Purna Avatar of Lord Dattatreya.With much archaeological value, this became a major pilgrim spot for many Shri Dattatrey devotees. Also, there is a confluence of the two rivers Panchganga and Krishna.</string>
    <string name="nar_fest1">1.Datta Jayanti</string>
    <string name="nar_fest2">2.Narasimha Jayanti is celebrated in the Hindu calendar Pushya month</string>
    <string name="nar_fest3">3.Gopal Kala Utsav is celebrated from Magha Poornima to Phalguna Panchami.</string>
    <string name="nar_fest4">4.Sripada Srivallabha Jayanthi is celebrated in Badrapada Masa on Ganesha Chaturthi Day</string>
    <string name="nar_hist">Shri Nrusinha saraswati swamy stayed in this area with full of Oudumber trees for 12 years and he flourished this region. Shri Nrusinh saraswati while travelling after completing Chaturmas at Oudumber, reached this place . The place has natural beauty and refreshing scenery due to confluence of Krishna and Panchaganga and thick forests of Audumber trees. The Paduka established by Swami are there in that temple. The Pancha Ganga Sagar, which is the confluence of the five holy rivers, Siva, Bhadra, Kumbhi, Bhagwati and Saraswati, where they all meet and merge in the Krishna river</string>
    <string name="nar_time">05.00 am: Paduka Puja, 08.00 am to 12.00 pm: Rudrabhishek</string>


    <!-- Restaurant-->
    //Solanki Cold Drinks
    <string name="sol_about">This pretty little joint is situated adjacent to the famous Mahalaxmi Temple of Kolhapur and brings forth a wide range of refreshing drinks for you to enjoy. Along with drinks, this place offers a nice variety of ice-creams and desserts. Pamper your sweet tooth by indulging in the yummy items that Solanki has in store. The dishes here are prepared with the amalgamation of unique flavors and ingredients which add a curious touch to it. The most-preferred items here include Falooda, Cocktail Ice-cream, and Ginger Soda. The ambiance exudes a youthful vibe,</string>
    <string name="sol_loc"> 1552-C, Laxmipuri, Near Shahu Talkiz, Kolhapur</string>
    <string name="sol_open"> 9:00 AM - 12:00 AM</string>
    <string name="sol_miss1">1.Coffee Beer</string>
    <string name="sol_miss2">2.Ice-cream mocktails</string>
    <string name="sol_miss3">3.Cakes</string>
    <string name="sol_two">INR 400</string>

    //Pahunchar
    <string name="pah_about">Situated in the Rajarampuri area of Kolhapur, this upbeat place is worth a visit.Take your family out for an enjoyable dinner to Pahunchar and indulge in the tempting dishes that it has in store. The carefully-crafted menu offers quite a number of options covering various regional cuisines. Go for the wholesome Maharashtrian Thali which comes in a huge platter containing various items ranging from curries to desserts. Also, do not miss out on their Bhakari and Buttermilk which are truly flavorsome. The ambiance is very homely, making it ideal for a family outing. Spend quality time with your kids and pamper them with appetizing dishes</string>
    <string name="pah_loc"> Kumudini Apartments, Near Union Bank, Bus Route, 5th lane, Rajarampuri, Kolhapur</string>
    <string name="pah_open">11:30 AM - 3:00 PM</string>
    <string name="pah_miss1">1.Kolhapuri Chicken</string>
    <string name="pah_miss2">2.Thali, Kolhapuri Veg</string>
    <string name="pah_miss3">3.Tambda-Pandara</string>
    <string name="pah_two">INR 400</string>
    Patlacha wada
    <string name="wad_about">Positioned opposite to Collector Office in Nagala Park, the gleaming exteriors of this restaurant are appealing enough to catch the eye of any visitor who passes by this vicinity. Embellished by colorful lighting all around the restaurant, this place is an absolute charmer. Take delight in the elegant décor of this place, augmented by its imposing structure. If you are looking for an extravagant place to dine in, this is the perfect destination. The service here is equally praiseworthy</string>
    <string name="wad_loc"> Anant Vishwa Tower, Near Collector Office, Assembly Road, Nagala Park, Kolhapur</string>
    <string name="wad_open">11:00 AM - 11:00 PM</string>
    <string name="wad_miss1">1.Lavani Chicken</string>
    <string name="wad_miss2">2.Goli Pulav</string>
    <string name="wad_miss3">3.Tambda-Pandara</string>
    <string name="wad_two">INR 300</string>
    //Little Italy
    <string name="lit_about">If you hold a fetish for Italian delicacies, this is just the right place to be in. Staying true to its name, Little Italy is a miniature version of Italy exuding a flamboyant vibe. The moment you step into this chic restaurant, you will be delivered to an entirely different world. The dazzling décor of this place is what lures most customers into it. Take some time out from your busy schedule and visit this restaurant for a memorable experience. Splurge on the vast assortment of items available here and enjoy a fine dining experience with your loved ones. </string>
    <string name="lit_loc"> Hotel Panchshil 517 A-2, Shivaji Park, Kolhapur</string>
    <string name="lit_open">11:30 AM - 11:30 PM</string>
    <string name="lit_miss1">1.Pasta</string>
    <string name="lit_miss2">2.1Pizza
</string>

    <string name="lit_two">INR 550</string>
    //Moon Tree Cafe
    <string name="mon_about">Located conveniently on the Pune-Bangalore Highway, this in-house restaurant installed inside Hotel Sayaji is a must-visit if you are traveling to Kolhapur. With an open-air setting and fascinating ambiance, this Cafe stands out as a much sought-after place among tourists. Feel amazed by the grandeur that Moon Tree exudes with its regal décor and elegant charm. Soothe your senses by breathing in the fresh breeze as you treat your eyes with the mesmerizing view that lies ahead of you. Be it a business meeting, a romantic dinner, a family outing or a casual hang-out, this place promises to be an ideal site for any occasion.</string>
    <string name="mon_loc"> 2104/15, Hotel Sayaji, Old Pune - Bangalore Highway, E Tararani Chowk, E Ward, Kolhapur</string>
    <string name="mon_open">9:30 AM - 9:00 PM</string>
    <string name="mon_miss1">1Cappuccino</string>
    <string name="mon_miss2">2.Pasta,</string>
    <string name="mon_two">INR 600</string>






    <!--Aurangabad Division-->
      <!--Aurangabad info-->
    <!--Forts Info-->
    // Daulatabad Fort
    <string name="dau_desc">One of the most commanding and undefeatable forts in the entire country, Daulatabad Fort in Daulatabad; or Devagiri as it was known earlier, is among the must-visit places near Aurangabad. Around 11 km north-west of Aurangabad, this glorious fortress stands strong on a conical hill that stands around 200 m above the sea level.Looking back into the history of the fort, you will realize its importance and strength. Compared to the other forts within or far from the region, the defense of Daulatabad Fort was very strong.</string>
    <string name="dau_loc">MH SH 22, Daulatabad, Maharashtra 431002</string>
    <string name="dau_time"> 8 AM to 6 PM</string>
    <string name="dau_road">Aurangabad is the nearest city to reach Daulatabad Fort. Aurangabad is well connected by roadways from major cities of Maharashtra and direct state transport buses are available from cities like Mumbai, Pune, Nashik to reach Aurangabad.Further from Aurangabad, there are regular bus services to reach Daulatabad Fort. Tourists can also hire a private cab to reach the Devgiri fort. It is just a half-hour drive from Aurangabad to Dulatabad Fort.</string>

    //Sunheri Mahal, Aurangabad
   <string name="sun_desc"></string>

</resources>