<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Explore_Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="first_slide_title">Search Your location</string>
    <string name="second_slide_title">Make a Call</string>
    <string name="third_slide_title">Add Missing Place</string>
    <string name="fourth_slide_title">Sit Back And Enjoy</string>
    <string name="fifth_slide_title">------------------------------------------------</string>

    <string name="first_slide_desc">You can Search any place nearby or within Maharashtra. We will display specific or all search related result.</string>
    <string name="second_slide_desc">We provide  almost all thr numbers of all department and shop registerd with us. You can make call with those department</string>
    <string name="third_slide_desc">If you have a shop or something and want to be a part of our growing industry then add your place by your Own.</string>
    <string name="fourth_slide_desc">We will handle everything for you. As you have the app in your pocket then you do not have to worry.</string>

    <!-- Temple Name-->
    00 AM - 8:00 PM</string>

    <!--Thane Dist-->
    <!--Forts-->
    //Bassein Fort
    <string name="bas_desc">Located in Vasai village of Thane District, this fort is visited by a number of people for its architecture and marvel features. As per history, this fort belonged to the Arab Sultanate of Cambay and was under the control of the Portuguese in the early 1400s. It was initially known as the The fort of St. Sebastian of Vasai and became the headquarters of the Portuguese Captain. With time, it was once owned by the Maratha clans and later ceded to the Britishers.</string>
    <string name="bas_ad">Killa Rd, Police Colony, Vasai West, Vasai-Virar, Maharashtra 401201</string>
    <string name="bas_built">Seuna (Yadava) dynasty</string>
    <string name="bas_reach">Looking for the nearest stop or station to Fort Bassein? Check out this list of stops closest to your destination: Chimaji Appa Smarak; Vasai Tehsil Office.</string>
    //Hirakot Fort
    <string name="hir_desc">One of the other historic fort in Thane is the Diamond or Hirakot fort. This fort was earlier used as the town jail. Later it was used as a emigration depot by the Mauritius government. Today the fort houses the offices of Police Inspector and the Prant officer.</string>
    <string name="hir_ad">Police Line, Alibag, Maharashtra 402201</string>
    <string name="hir_built"> The hirakot fort was built by the marathas</string>
    <string name="hir_reach">From mumdai, hirakot fort is about 95km away by road and you can travel via nh 66. from pune, this destination is about 142km away and can be reached using bengaluru - mumbai hwy/mumbai - pune hwy/mumbai - pune expy.</string>
    //Kelva Fort
    <string name="kel_desc">Another masterpiece built by the Portuguese in 16th century, this fort is situated on the Kelva beach and is surrounded by the palmy green Suru trees. This fort is surrounded by water bodies and is well known to look more spectacular during high tides.</string>
    <string name="Kel_ad">Kelwa Jangera, Kelwa, Maharashtra</string>
    <string name="kel_built">fort constructed by Portuguese </string>
    <string name="kel_reach">Kelva Beach is situated only at a distance of 80km from Mumbai and can be easily reached either by taking the Mumbai-Ahmedabad Highway No. 8 to Vasai – Safale Road or Manor – Palghar road to Manor via Borivali – Dahisar.The beach is close to the Sitla Devi temple which is also a popular tourist attraction here.</string>
    //Ghodbunder Fort
    <string name="gho_desc">Located in Ghodbunder village, Thane, Ghodbunder Fort is known for its age old heritage. It was built back in 1730 by the Portuguese and was  earlier known as Cacabe De Tanna. In 1737, the Marathas took over the fort from the Portuguese. It was later captured by Britishers and used as a headquarter for district administration. Currently due to the ruins, the fort is under government for preservation and renovation purposes.</string>
    <string name="gho_ad">Ghodbander Village, Ghodbunder, Mira Bhayandar, Maharashtra 401107</string>
    <string name="gho_built">he fort was built in 1730 by the Portuguese </string>
    <string name="gho_reach">Located on one of the hills near Ullas river, Ghodbunder Fort is one of the major historical tourist attractions in Maharashtra. Ghodbander fort is on the Ghodbander Road in Ghodbunder village, located at a distance of 24.4 km from thane railway station. One can take the Thane Borivli route from thane to reach the fort. </string>

    <!--Temple-->
    //VAJRESHWARI TEMPLE
    <string name="var_desc">Vajreshwari Temple is one of the oldest temples in Thane. It is an ancient temple that was built in 1739, based on Vasai Fort architecture. The visitors and devotees can surround the ramparts and bastions and can get the feeling of God when entering the fort. Vajreshwari Temple features a congregation hall, sanctum, and the sanatorium. This temple will be the place where you can realise the Puranas (Hindu scriptures) the area of Vadvali described as being visited by Avatars (incarnations) includes The Akloli and Ganeshpuri hot springs are well known.</string>
    <string name="var_spec">Deepavali, Festival Celebrations, Chitra Amavasya, Holi, Navratri Festival, Shri Dattajayanti, Godhadebaba Shrine Worship, Hanuman Jayanti, Religious Site, Poojas, Kojagiri Pournima and Prasadam</string>
    <string name="var_time">Mon-Sun: 5:30am - 9pm</string>
    //KOPINESHWAR MANDIR
    <string name="kopi_desc">Kopineshwar Mandir is a renowned temple where one of Maharashtra state biggest Shivalinga is present. This temple is built with a diameter of 5 feet and is 5 feet tall. It is also considered to be one of the most sacred temples of supporters in the area. The temple is visited by many local devotees and tourists throughout the year. Kopineshwar Mandir was built by the Shilahara Dynasty, which faced restoration in the year 1760. The temple is set in a tranquil environment, which allows the visitors and devotees to enjoy a peaceful ambience with the gods presence.</string>
    <string name="kopi_spec">Programs, Celebrations, Hindu Temple, Architectural Structure, Events, Poojas, Festivals and Historical Places</string>
    <string name="kopi_time">Mon-Sun: 6am - 9pm</string>
    //SAIBABA TEMPLE
    <string name="sai_desc">Saibaba Temple in Thane is a Chota Shirdi which is one of the famous Sai temples in Thane. The temple faces thousands of devotees and visitors throughout the year. The idol in the temple is a replica of Shirdi Sai temple. This temple honours Sai Vardhapan Din for which a vast group of devotees gathers to celebrate it every year. Saibaba Temple performs daily, and special poojas; which also happens on festival days. Sai Baba devotees find this temple to be a calm and pleasing place. The temple is also one of the temples that houses a beautiful smiling face of Sai Baba.</string>
    <string name="sai_spec">Festival Celebration, Special Poojas, Performances, Historical Places, Prasadam, Anadhanam, Hindu Temple, Sacred and Religious Sites</string>
    <string name="sai_time"> Mon-Sat: 10am - 6pm Sun: Closed</string>
    //Ganeshpuri Temple
    <string name="gan_desc">This is a small town near Bhiwandi, about 40 km from Thane which is the residence of Swami Nityananda Maharaj. An ancient temple is also there with four tanks called kundas. The kundas are some 800 years old. It is more famous for its hot water springs. Legend has it that Sage Vashist did a yagna to propitiate Lord Ganesh here, hence the name Ganeshpuri.</string>
    <string name="gan_spec">Around 1936 when Nityananda baba came to Ganeshpuri from vajreshwari, He found this water springs and developed it to welcome villagers to have bath declaring it as sacred. </string>
    <string name="gan_time">Mon-Sun: 4:22am - 9:30pm</string>
    //Manas Jain Temple
    <string name="man_desc">Manas Mandir is a beautiful place. It is in between Vasind and Asangoan. Shri Bhuvan Bhanu Jain Manas Mandir Tirtha, is situated at village savroli, in Shahapur taluka of Thane district of Maharashtra. It is around 85 kms from Mumbai and 45 kms from Thane and 30 kms from Bhiwandi.</string>
    <string name="man_spec">Very nice place for a family trip. Very quite premises and well maintained. The place is spread across a really large area with trees and greenery everywhere. We missed the lunch but had tea with mathri which was very tasty.</string>
    <string name="man_time">6:00 AM - 8:00 PM</string>

    <!--Lake-->
    //Masunda lake
    <string name="mas_desc">This beautiful lake is located on the East side of Thane, in the heart of the city. It is surrounded by important historic places like Gadkari Rangayatan, St. John church, Kopineshwar temple, and Jambli market. People go there for boating, tonga rides, to munch on bhelpuri and indulge in other touristy things the place to offer.</string>
    <string name="mas_his"> Earlier the Masunda Lake extended up to the Kopineshwar Mandir in the east but in the 1950s, the construction of a new road drastically reduced its area.</string>
    //Kachrali Lake
    <string name="kach_desc">Spread across 2 hectares, it is situated bang opposite the civic headquarters. This is a restored water body and at night it lights up to be even more beautiful. Youngsters and senior citizens often prefer to chill by this lake.</string>
    <string name="kach_his">There is a temple of Lord Ganesh inside the lake premises. Once a slum area, major cleansing and beautification has transformed it to a joggers paradise. The government has brought Ducks on the lake, these ducks can be seen in the lake especially on the one tree island.</string>
    //Makhmali lake
    <string name="mak_desc">With an area of about one hectare, this lake is comparatively smaller. But it is beautiful nonetheless. As the name suggests, makhmali which literally means smooth, this smooth lake body is near the Uthalsar Ward office. It has a marriage hall in the background and at night when it is lit, it is a sight to behold. It also has a small garden area.</string>
    <string name="mak_his">makhmali lake, Thane is a perfect destination for a great time with your dear ones. Enjoy the attractions of this popular tourist spot. With so much to lure your senses and offer you recreation at its best, get drenched in the spirit of adventure that you get to explore at makhmali lake, Thane. Enjoy together all the points of popular interests and bring back several memorable moments. makhmali lake.</string>
    // Upvan Lake
    <string name="up_desc">This is touted to be the most beautiful lake in the city. With Yeoor hills set against as a backdrop, it is located at the foothills of Thanes hill station. This lake is especially popular amongst young couples. It is a lovers lake. *wink*</string>
    <string name="up_his">Environed by the majestic hills of Yeoor, the Eco-friendly Upvan lake is the largest of its kind in Thane of Maharashtra. Built and revamped by J. K. Singhania with the sole objective of supplying water to the Raymonf factory, the lake became a primal water supplier to the entire city of Thane.</string>
    //Bramhala Lake
    <string name="bra_desc">It is one of the oldest lakes of Thane and was revamped a few years ago. Post the uplift, a jogger’s track added, the garden is pruned and maintained regularly, this lake is breathtaking. People who seek calmness, head here and spend some time by it. It is opposite Babubhai Petrol Pump in Uthalsar Ward Committee.</string>
    <string name="bra_his">The lakes in Thane bring nature close to the residents; therefore people are choosing to settle in Thane. Also the huge infrastructural development taking place all around the city has made it a people’s choice. Thane is the perfect spot away from the crowded suburbs of Mumbai, where people can enjoy in the womb of nature. Numerous malls, apartments, commercial spaces and transportation facilities are being developed all around the city to make the lifestyle of the citizens convenient and resourceful.</string>


    <string name="tourism_mobile_apps_help_users_for_planning_travel_accommodation_bookings_ticket_bookings_cab_booking_route_mapping_and_more">Tourism Mobile apps help users for planning travel, accommodation bookings, ticket bookings, cab booking, route mapping, and more. </string>
    <string name="however_these_are_just_the_basic_uses_of_tourism_mobile_apps_and_more_tourist_services_can_be_delivered">However, these are just the basic uses of tourism mobile apps, and more tourist services can be delivered</string>
</resources>
